好吧，让我们来看看，因为您知道第二个家庭作业的时间更少了
all right let's see as you know the second homework has less time for you to
second homework has less time for you to work simply because I want to be sure
工作只是因为我想确保我们至少涵盖6项作业9我
work simply because I want to be sure that we at least cover 6 homework 9 I
that we at least cover 6 homework 9 I noticed some of you don't bother about
注意到你们中有些人不理会功课，因为您正在审核
noticed some of you don't bother about homework because you're auditing the
homework because you're auditing the class disappointed to hear that okay
上课让我失望了
我们回家后的建议，大多数人都会不断回顾，因为当我得到时
homework because you're auditing the class disappointed to hear that okay
a recommendation when we post home most keep revisiting them because when I get
我们回家后的建议，大多数人都会不断回顾，因为当我得到时
keep revisiting them because when I get comments from students from when I look
当我回头看时，学生们的评论我直接去了，谁改变了他们的
comments from students from when I look back I go directly and who changes their
back I go directly and who changes their and I don't want to keep sending
我不想继续发送邮件说我们改变了那个
and I don't want to keep sending messages saying we change this and that
messages saying we change this and that so please you know look on the website
所以请您了解网站上的更改，这样我们就谈到了
so please you know look on the website for changes okay so we talked about the
for changes okay so we talked about the elimination algorithm last week both for
上周针对有向图或无向图的消除算法以及今天
elimination algorithm last week both for directed or undirected graphs and today
directed or undirected graphs and today we want sort of to revisit the
我们想重新考虑消除算法，但是将其放在
we want sort of to revisit the elimination algorithm but put it on a
elimination algorithm but put it on a form that is related to what's called
与所谓的消息传递和Beyonder相关的形式
form that is related to what's called message passing and the Beyonder that
message passing and the Beyonder that goes through this name is called the
经历这个名字叫做算法的压模，本质上是
goes through this name is called the Stamper of the algorithm in essence is
Stamper of the algorithm in essence is the same sort of a state elimination
相同的状态消除算法，但阅读方式更多
the same sort of a state elimination algorithm but read people way more
algorithm but read people way more efficient depending on what type of so
效率取决于哪种类型，因此我们将首先应用它来扭转
efficient depending on what type of so we're going to apply this first to twist
we're going to apply this first to twist and then next week we will extend it to
然后下周我们将其扩展到一般图形，因此实际上在我们应用时
and then next week we will extend it to general graph so actually when we apply
general graph so actually when we apply it brings me we see that this algorithms
它带给我，我们看到这种算法确实是非常令人难以置信的项目，因此
it brings me we see that this algorithms are really exact incredible items so
are really exact incredible items so there are no proximation to be done
没有正确的选择，所以让我提出一些建议
there are no proximation to be done right so let me bring out some of the
right so let me bring out some of the basic ideas we have seen with the
我们已经在消除算法中看到了一些基本思想，所以这是
basic ideas we have seen with the elimination algorithm so here is the
elimination algorithm so here is the directed graph 5 note this is the
有向图5注意这是关节的分解总数
directed graph 5 note this is the decomposition of the joint the total
decomposition of the joint the total ization of the joint applied by the
该图所应用的关节的化，可以说是推论
ization of the joint applied by the graph and let's say that the inference
graph and let's say that the inference asked that were interested is to compute
询问是否有兴趣计算给定资本的支付概率
asked that were interested is to compute the probability of pay given the Capital
the probability of pay given the Capital steez needle stick okay so you know so
steez针刺好，所以您知道，这实际上是我们遇到的问题
steez needle stick okay so you know so this is the problem actually we have
this is the problem actually we have discussed up to now for several lectures
到目前为止，我们已经讨论了几次讲座，所以很明显，您知道您知道您可以
discussed up to now for several lectures so obviously you know you know you can
so obviously you know you know you can start completing this conditional using
开始使用此因式分解完成此条件，这将
start completing this conditional using this factorization and this is going to
this factorization and this is going to be elective process so let's check how
是选修过程，所以让我们检查一下如何使用20个
be elective process so let's check how you're going to do this with 20 of
you're going to do this with 20 of resistance so to complete this you will
阻力，因此要完成此操作，您将需要计算联合平面三
resistance so to complete this you will need to compute the jointer plane three
need to compute the jointer plane three divided by the probability of capital C
除以资本C作为计算联合的受托人的概率
divided by the probability of capital C being the trustee to compute the joint
being the trustee to compute the joint of a entity series and evidence killed
实体系列的证据和被杀死的证据等于小T显然你要走
of a entity series and evidence killed equal to little T obviously you're going
equal to little T obviously you're going to have to take this join distribution
必须采用这种ABCDE的联合发行方式，并且将BD边缘化
to have to take this join distribution of ABCDE and marginalize out BD any so
of ABCDE and marginalize out BD any so you have to perform this operation of
您必须在这里执行此操作，如果我们假设这些
you have to perform this operation of this here and if we assume that these
this here and if we assume that these variables are all binary you will need
变量都是二进制的，您将需要B中的两个项这两个项
variables are all binary you will need two terms from B two terms for these two
two terms from B two terms for these two terms for e so eight terms and you need
八个e项，您需要为每个项计算相同的项
terms for e so eight terms and you need to compute the same terms for each of
to compute the same terms for each of the values of a which are two so this
a的值是2，所以此计算是16次运算，所以这
the values of a which are two so this calculation is 16 operation okay so this
calculation is 16 operation okay so this is what you seal the you know the
是密封的东西，您知道这里的分子来计算它，您将
is what you seal the you know the numerator here to compute this you will
numerator here to compute this you will have to do marginalization a okay so
必须做一个边缘化，所以这是两个操作并计算
have to do marginalization a okay so that's two operations and to compute
that's two operations and to compute this ratio you have to compute this for
您必须为每个薪水值计算该比率才能进行操作
this ratio you have to compute this for every value of pay in order to operation
every value of pay in order to operation so if the calculation count is correct
因此，如果计算计数正确，则基本上需要执行20个操作
so if the calculation count is correct you need 20 operations basically to do
you need 20 operations basically to do this right so the more efficient method
这项权利，因此我们在讨论时基于消除的更有效方法
this right so the more efficient method based on the elimination when we discuss
based on the elimination when we discuss is to actually compute this by pushing
是通过推进一些求和来实际计算这个，所以现在如果
is to actually compute this by pushing forward some of the summation so now if
forward some of the summation so now if you notice I put the semester only on
你注意到我只把这个学期放在对投资者的这种危险保留上
you notice I put the semester only on this peril reservation on the investor
this peril reservation on the investor all the terms come from the factories
所有的术语都来自联合的工厂和魔术，因为
all the terms come from the factories ation of the joint and by magic because
ation of the joint and by magic because these are conditional distributions this
这些是条件分布，这一项等于1，这一项等于
these are conditional distributions this term is equal to 1 this term is equal to
term is equal to 1 this term is equal to 1 and the only thing you have to compute
1，而您唯一需要计算的就是扫盲，所以B的两个值
1 and the only thing you have to compute is literation right so two values of B
is literation right so two values of B and you have to compute them for two
并且您必须为两个值计算它们才能支付，这仅适用于
and you have to compute them for two values to pay this is only for
values to pay this is only for operations and if you look back this was
操作，如果回头看，这是16个操作，所以基本上
operations and if you look back this was 16 operations right so basically the
16 operations right so basically the elimination algorithm now allows us to
消除算法现在允许我们计算像这样的边际事物
elimination algorithm now allows us to compute this marginals things like this
compute this marginals things like this in a way more efficient way than just
比您了解多代使用更有效的方式
in a way more efficient way than just doing you know multi-generation using
doing you know multi-generation using this factorization implied by the graph
该图暗示的因式分解好吧，如果您不这样做，则进行20次操作
this factorization implied by the graph alright so 20 operations if you don't do
alright so 20 operations if you don't do anything special if you use the
如果您针对此定向使用消除算法，则有什么特别的
anything special if you use the elimination algorithm for this directed
elimination algorithm for this directed graph you only get this in eight
图中，您只能在8个操作中获得8个操作，因为
graph you only get this in eight operations eight operations because this
operations eight operations because this is for than the other two steps are
比其他两个步骤基本相同，因此有一个
is for than the other two steps are basically identical less so there is a
basically identical less so there is a problem with this algorithms with
该算法与消除算法的问题，问题是
problem with this algorithms with elimination algorithm and the problem is
elimination algorithm and the problem is that we focus on calculating one
我们专注于计算一种边际或无条件的分布
that we focus on calculating one marginal or unconditional distribution
marginal or unconditional distribution of the time all right so in this problem
在这个问题上，如果假设您的目标是
of the time all right so in this problem if let's say your objective is to
if let's say your objective is to calculate I don't know the probability
计算我不知道被条纹一棵小树的可能性
calculate I don't know the probability of being given streak one little tree
of being given streak one little tree you will have to repeat this from
您将不得不从头开始重复
you will have to repeat this from scratch
scratch that's waste of time so the algorithms
那是浪费时间，所以我们今天将要讨论的算法是
that's waste of time so the algorithms we will discuss today is how do we
we will discuss today is how do we complete not just let's say one
完成不只是说一个条件
complete not just let's say one condition
or one marginal but other conditionals are all marginal in the graph all
或一个边际但其他条件在图中全部都是边际的
are all marginal in the graph all applaud so given the evidence
鼓掌，因此给定证据是什么的条件分布
applaud so given the evidence what's the conditional distribution of
what's the conditional distribution of 40 other notes okay one at the time can
好的40个其他的音符，一次可以使我们更有效地执行此操作，而无需
40 other notes okay one at the time can we do this more efficiently without
we do this more efficiently without having to repeat this for every case in
原则上必须针对每种情况重复此操作，我们可以进行一些计算
having to repeat this for every case in principle can we do some calculations
principle can we do some calculations that can be recycled as we compute one
在我们计算一次边际或一个条件时可以回收利用
that can be recycled as we compute one marginal or one conditional at the time
marginal or one conditional at the time can we recycle some calculations and the
我们可以回收一些计算和今天讨论的操作吗
can we recycle some calculations and the operation that we discuss today it's
operation that we discuss today it's basically sub chaser for the score
分数信念传播方法基本上是次追逐者，但是
basically sub chaser for the score belief propagation methods okay but
belief propagation methods okay but today what we will see is exactly the
今天我们将要看到的是技巧中的波传播，好吧，所以您
today what we will see is exactly the wave propagation in tricks okay so you
wave propagation in tricks okay so you will see mathematically there is really
将会在数学上看到关于我们将要做什么的确没有新技术
will see mathematically there is really no new techniques on what we will
no new techniques on what we will discuss but the algorithm is way more
讨论，但该算法使更多的基督徒和消除任何方式
discuss but the algorithm is way more Christians and elimination of so any
Christians and elimination of so any questions with what we have seen up to
关于我们到目前为止用消除算法看到的问题
questions with what we have seen up to now with the elimination algorithm for
now with the elimination algorithm for directed or undirected graphs okay so
有向图或无向图还可以，所以我会重复一遍
directed or undirected graphs okay so some kind of thing I have a repeat of
some kind of thing I have a repeat of the algorithm again but we still Isis
再次使用该算法，但我们仍然会继续使用Isis，因此您的想法是
the algorithm again but we still Isis will go so the idea is to you know
will go so the idea is to you know remember when we did the elimination
记得当我们执行消除算法时，我们计算了很多
remember when we did the elimination algorithm we calculated a lots of
algorithm we calculated a lots of intermediate factors so the adage can we
中间因素，因此格言可以真正使用那些静脉内因素来
intermediate factors so the adage can we really use those intravenous factors to
really use those intravenous factors to compute multiple Martinez at the same
同时计算多个Martinez，我们今天将执行此操作，但仅
compute multiple Martinez at the same time and we will do this today but only
time and we will do this today but only we will do this for priests and three
我们将针对牧师和三个相似的图形执行此操作
we will do this for priests and three like graphs
like graphs okay if you try to do this for general
好吧，如果您尝试对一般图形执行此操作，则算法基本上需要
okay if you try to do this for general graphs basically the algorithm needs to
graphs basically the algorithm needs to lots of modifications and the algorithm
大量的修改和算法，我们去一般的平均水平想要
lots of modifications and the algorithm we go the general average wanted the
we go the general average wanted the name Junction tree algorithm okay and we
命名结点树算法好，下周我们将讨论这个，所以
name Junction tree algorithm okay and we will discuss this next next week so
will discuss this next next week so right now we will concentrate on three
现在，我们将集中在三个立场，三个像图
right now we will concentrate on three stand three like graphs
stand three like graphs and we received wiser so let's turn
而且我们收到了更明智的信息，所以让我们用一点点来激发发生的事情
and we received wiser so let's turn motivate what's going on with a little
motivate what's going on with a little chain so let's say we have the joint
链，所以假设我们有x1到xn的联合分布，我们想要
chain so let's say we have the joint distribution of x1 to xn and we want to
distribution of x1 to xn and we want to compute the marginal distribution of
计算文学笔记的边际分布程度，但是我们想要
compute the marginal distribution of literary note the extent but we wanted
literary note the extent but we wanted to compute in a way that will allow us
进行计算的方式使我们几乎没有额外的计算成本
to compute in a way that will allow us almost no additional costs to compute
almost no additional costs to compute the marginal support of the other notes
其他笔记的边际支持，所以我们要这样做
the marginal support of the other notes as well so we're going to do this
as well so we're going to do this calculation in a little bit more
计算比以前更有效
calculation in a little bit more efficient way than we have done before
efficient way than we have done before so perfect I am taking the maximal
如此完美，我在这里采取了最大的派系-或为此法案，所以我
so perfect I am taking the maximal cliques here - or for this bill so I
cliques here - or for this bill so I write the effectors this undirected
写效应器，这个无向图就是节点1和
write the effectors this undirected graph is the potential of the nodes 1 &amp;
graph is the potential of the nodes 1 &amp; 2 2 &amp; 3 and minus 1 and then and and
2 2＆3和负1，然后和，因为这些不是概率
2 2 &amp; 3 and minus 1 and then and and because these are not probabilities
because these are not probabilities argue the factorization I use the an
争论因式分解，我使用那里的组织因数T来照顾
argue the factorization I use the an organization factor T there to take care
organization factor T there to take care but this product basically one of us he
但是这个产品基本上是我们中的一个，他给了我一个很好的价值，所以这个家伙
but this product basically one of us he gives me a value all right so this guy
gives me a value all right so this guy in the question below
在下面的问题中，这是一种消除算法
in the question below it's sort of an elimination algorithm
it's sort of an elimination algorithm but very much different from what we
但与我们迄今为止所消除的情况有很大不同
but very much different from what we have seen up to now with the elimination
have seen up to now with the elimination both of the resident of directed graphs
都是有向图的居民，所以我想让你看一下这个方程
both of the resident of directed graphs so I want you to look at this equation
so I want you to look at this equation and tell me what is different you know
告诉我有什么不同，你知道这我在顶部有两个词，
and tell me what is different you know this I have two terms one on the top and
this I have two terms one on the top and one on the bottom
底部的一个好吧，我提醒您扩展
one on the bottom alright and I remind you the extend
alright and I remind you the extend means I have to integrate on all
意味着我必须在所有变量上进行整合，这是我的程度
means I have to integrate on all variables what extent and this is what I
variables what extent and this is what I have done here but I have done it in
已经在这里完成了，但是我已经按照特定的顺序完成了，所以我希望你能够
have done here but I have done it in some specific order so I want you to
some specific order so I want you to tell me what this is special there in
告诉我顺序中有什么特别之处，与有什么不同
tell me what this is special there in the order and how is that different from
the order and how is that different from before so the node exchange some quality
在此之前，节点在中间的某个地方交换了一些质量，但没有
before so the node exchange some quality on the middle somewhere there it doesn't
on the middle somewhere there it doesn't have to be in the middle but it's
必须在中间，但介于两者之间
have to be in the middle but it's somewhere in between
所以在第一次总结中，我从右到左开始
so on the first summation I am starting something from the right to the left
something from the right to the left from summing from x1 to x2 to xn minus 1
从x1到x2到xn减1，所以我从X传播信息
from summing from x1 to x2 to xn minus 1 so I am propagating information from X
so I am propagating information from X run all the way to excel all right and
一直运行以达到最佳效果，现在在底部的汇总中查看
run all the way to excel all right and look now in the summation on the bottom
look now in the summation on the bottom I have rearranged it in such a way that
我以第一个终端Excel然后在XX上的方式重新安排了它
I have rearranged it in such a way that the first terminal Excel then on X X
the first terminal Excel then on X X capital n the next capital n minus 1 all
大写n下一个大写n减1一直扩展，所以我传播
capital n the next capital n minus 1 all the way to extend so I propagate
the way to extend so I propagate information from X capital n to excess
X资本n到多余的信息，所以我从右边传播到
information from X capital n to excess so I propagate from the right to the
so I propagate from the right to the next step so there is a portable
下一步，以便将信息便携式传播到节点XN
next step so there is a portable propagation of information to node X N
propagation of information to node X N and there is a marker propagation of
并且从最后一个节点X大写开始有信息的标记传播
and there is a marker propagation of information from the last node X capital
information from the last node X capital of time ok so this is not similar to
时间还可以，所以这与我们消除淘汰的方式不同
of time ok so this is not similar to what we did with the elimination
what we did with the elimination algorithm right where we start
正确的算法，我们从这里开始以某些顺序消除
algorithm right where we start eliminating with some order here we are
eliminating with some order here we are sending messages from the left and we
从左边发送消息，我们从右边发送消息，
sending messages from the left and we are sending message from the right and
are sending message from the right and I'm going to define what this messages
我将定义此消息是什么，实际上是要开始的定义
I'm going to define what this messages are and actually the definition to start
are and actually the definition to start with the message that is being sent from
从左边发送到节点X n的消息在此处表示为mu
with the message that is being sent from the left to node X n is denoted here mu
the left to node X n is denoted here mu alpha of X 10 is the function of xn is
X 10的alpha基本上是xn的函数，或者是所有n的乘积
alpha of X 10 is the function of xn is basically or is the product of all the
basically or is the product of all the potentials to the left of the node X 10
节点X 10左侧的电位，其中的所有其他变量
potentials to the left of the node X 10 where all the other variables for the
where all the other variables for the chain have been some towers okay and if
连锁店有些塔楼还可以，如果mu beta是所有条款的父亲
chain have been some towers okay and if mu beta is the father of all the terms
mu beta is the father of all the terms to the right where everything has been
在右边，从xn加1到X大写n
to the right where everything has been somehow from xn plus 1 to X capital n
somehow from xn plus 1 to X capital n except little XL okay but it is not just
除了小号XL可以，但是在这里不仅仅是简单的定义
except little XL okay but it is not just simple definition here right the
simple definition here right the definition implies the destinations this
定义意味着以正确的方式进行此计算的目的地
definition implies the destinations this calculation happens in the proper way
calculation happens in the proper way that you see here that implies some
您在此处看到的内容暗示了此消息的某些递归关系
that you see here that implies some recursive relations for this message
recursive relations for this message this new
这个新的新测试版，我要写那些
this new new beta and I'm gonna write those
new beta and I'm gonna write those recursive relationship one second okay
递归关系一秒钟还可以，所以请仔细看一下这个方程
recursive relationship one second okay so look carefully at this equation earth
so look carefully at this equation earth right we define this to be mu alpha and
正确，我们将其定义为mu alpha，我在这里表示的基本上是我们称之为
right we define this to be mu alpha and I denoted here is basically we call it
I denoted here is basically we call it the masters that is tenth two from the
左起第十二位的大师，即alpha所使用的表示法
the masters that is tenth two from the left that's alpha the notation used by
left that's alpha the notation used by bishop to the node extent and mu beta is
主教到节点范围，而mu beta是注释发送到
bishop to the node extent and mu beta is the message sent by the notes to the
the message sent by the notes to the right of return okay
归还权好，定义就是您在此处看到的
right of return okay and the definition is what you see here
and the definition is what you see here and the master comes to be basically the
主人基本上就是新的alpha乘以mu beta的乘积
and the master comes to be basically the product of new alpha times mu beta
product of new alpha times mu beta divided by the normalization factor of Z
如果要计算，可以有效地除以Z的归一化因子
divided by the normalization factor of Z so effectively if you want to calculate
so effectively if you want to calculate with this definition the P of X then
有了这个定义，X的P，那么您需要做的就是计算
with this definition the P of X then what you need to do is calculate this
what you need to do is calculate this message me alpha by beta of Excel and
通过Excel beta向我发送消息，然后将其相乘并将其标准化
message me alpha by beta of Excel and then multiply them and normalize them
then multiply them and normalize them and you're done
在您给我幻灯片之前，您已完成此操作
and you're done so before it's in slide that I give you
so before it's in slide that I give you the the recursive relationship from your
您从Beta中获得的递归关系
the the recursive relationship from your from your beta can you just you know can
from your beta can you just you know can you guess the well the recursive
你猜得很好，你可以在这里采取递归关系，但我
you guess the well the recursive relation you can take here but what I
relation you can take here but what I was going to ask you well can you guess
本来想问你的好吗，你能猜到这如何减少信息
was going to ask you well can you guess how this can reduce information that the
how this can reduce information that the elimination algorithm could not do I
消除算法无法做到，我的意思是看这些
elimination algorithm could not do I mean look at this the way that these
mean look at this the way that these messages you know when you know this
当您知道这样的消息时，您知道的消息就是这样，您也
messages you know when you know this message like that right so it you also
message like that right so it you also but also I put the similar definition of
但我也将新Alpha X n减1的类似定义定义为
but also I put the similar definition of new Alpha X n minus 1 which will be the
new Alpha X n minus 1 which will be the product of all the potentials from the
我从x1向前走的时候，左边所有势的乘积
product of all the potentials from the left alright so as I go forward from x1
left alright so as I go forward from x1 to xn minus 1 with all the variables
到xn减1并消除了所有变量，但x10-左错误
to xn minus 1 with all the variables eliminated but the x10 - wrong left
eliminated but the x10 - wrong left totally okay so can you see a way where
完全可以，所以您能看到某种方式吗？
totally okay so can you see a way where somehow this one where it will be way
somehow this one where it will be way more efficient than integration are
比集成更有效，并且将允许我使用以下概念
more efficient than integration are and will allow me using this ideation of
and will allow me using this ideation of this derivation to compute the marginal
这种推导来计算图中所有节点的边际不是一个
this derivation to compute the marginal of all the nodes in the graph not one
of all the nodes in the graph not one but all what will be the new algorithm
但是如果可以的话，我们可以通过其他方式思考的新算法将是什么
but all what will be the new algorithm that we can think about in other ways if
that we can think about in other ways if my interest is not the marginal of X 10
我的兴趣不是X 10的边际，而是xn减去1的边际，
my interest is not the marginal of X 10 but the marginal of xn minus 1 according
but the marginal of xn minus 1 according to this derivation how do we compute the
对此推导，我们如何根据此计算xn减去1的边际
to this derivation how do we compute the marginal of xn minus 1 according to this
marginal of xn minus 1 according to this point will be
点将是
我在这里放了一些箭头我没有在这里放所有的箭头
marginal of xn minus 1 according to this point will be
I put some of the arrows here I haven't put all the arrows there so how do we
我在这里放了一些箭头我没有在这里放所有的箭头
put all the arrows there so how do we compute the marginal of xn minus 1 will
计算xn的边际减1将是Miller部分，其中的函数
compute the marginal of xn minus 1 will be Miller part of which the function of
be Miller part of which the function of xn minus 1 multiplied with me because
xn减去1乘以我，因为嵌套是从
xn minus 1 multiplied with me because the nest is that goes to xn minus 1 from
the nest is that goes to xn minus 1 from the right which is an arrow that would
右边的是一个箭头，这将是正确的消息
the right which is an arrow that would be message that goes this way correct
be message that goes this way correct this different ways
我成为这种不同方式的无噪音算法
this different ways noiseless algorithm that I come to be
noiseless algorithm that I come to be more efficient what the algorithm is
更有效的算法将是什么样子，这将使我能够
more efficient what the algorithm is going to be like that will allow me to
going to be like that will allow me to compute all the marginals that was well
计算所有很好的边际，算法将完成所有
compute all the marginals that was well the algorithm will be complete all the
the algorithm will be complete all the messages it's forward from left right
消息从左到右向前计算所有消息从
messages it's forward from left right compute all the messages backwards from
compute all the messages backwards from right to left and then basically you go
从右到左，然后基本上您可以走到任何节点，您实际上可以计算
right to left and then basically you go at any node and you actually can compute
at any node and you actually can compute the the marginals by multiplying the
通过乘以至少到达更新的消息来增加边际
the the marginals by multiplying the messages arriving the update at least
messages arriving the update at least know they often veto messages and the
知道他们经常否决消息，并且归一化因素是他们多少次
know they often veto messages and the normalization factor how many times they
normalization factor how many times they have to compute it you know they scared
必须计算它，您知道他们害怕得很好，我没有像
have to compute it you know they scared well I did not put Z annulation like
well I did not put Z annulation like that but you know the organization
但是，您知道组织粒子经常会有罗马化
that but you know the organization particle often we have the romanization
particle often we have the romanization factor actually comes here from query
因素实际上来自查询，来自于联合，所以如何
factor actually comes here from query comes from here from the joint so how
comes from here from the joint so how many times you know the romanization
很多时候，您知道在这种情况下需要检查的罗马化因子是
many times you know the romanization factor with check for this case would be
factor with check for this case would be take this product sum it up for all
将这个乘积求和为X 10节T的所有值，那么你多久一次
take this product sum it up for all values of X 10 knots T so how often you
values of X 10 knots T so how often you have to compute
必须计算
像是xn减去1 4 X 1 X大写n的另一个归一化因子
values of X 10 knots T so how often you have to compute
like we'd be another normalization factor for xn minus 1 4 X 1 X capital n
像是xn减去1 4 X 1 X大写n的另一个归一化因子
factor for xn minus 1 4 X 1 X capital n no so so 6 computed what okay so what we
否，所以6计算了好吗，所以我们现在需要做的是看这是否
no so so 6 computed what okay so what we need to do now is we need to see if this
need to do now is we need to see if this definition of new alpha and the
可以编写新的alpha的定义和新的beta的定义
definition of new alpha and the definition of new beta can be written
definition of new beta can be written down in a way that is sort of recursive
以某种递归的方式向下移动，这样您就可以拥有一个不错的角度，所以让我们
down in a way that is sort of recursive so you can have a nice angle so let's
so you can have a nice angle so let's concentrate on me all right so on so the
好吧，专心于我，所以这里的新Alpha也是你知道的
concentrate on me all right so on so the new alpha here is also you know this
new alpha here is also you know this summation of everything except extend of
除延展左侧所有势能的延展外，所有事物的总和
summation of everything except extend of all the potentials to the left of extend
all the potentials to the left of extend okay so summation of xn minus 1 and
好吧，所以xn的总和减去1，在这里某处xn的抽取
okay so summation of xn minus 1 and somewhere here the decimation of xn
somewhere here the decimation of xn minus 2 etc I want you to think visually
减2等，我想让您以视觉的方式思考这个定义
minus 2 etc I want you to think visually all right looking on on this definition
all right looking on on this definition here I'm gonna have summation of xn
在这里，我将得到xn减去2然后是X和减去3然后是X 1的总和
here I'm gonna have summation of xn minus 2 then X and minus 3 and then X 1
minus 2 then X and minus 3 and then X 1 can you tell me more about summation
你能告诉我更多关于从xn减2开始的求和的意思吗？
can you tell me more about summation starting from xn minus 2 what is that
starting from xn minus 2 what is that what's the name of of summation if the
求和的名称是什么，如果它的名称是Excel以外的纽约，则
what's the name of of summation if the name of this is New York off Excel the
name of this is New York off Excel the deen-ul-haq
Deen-ul-haq
呼气减一，所以基本上是操作系统的封装
name of this is New York off Excel the deen-ul-haq
exhale minus one so basically the encapsulation for the operating system
呼气减一，所以基本上是操作系统的封装
encapsulation for the operating system right so if you want to compute me Ralph
正确，因此，如果您要计算Ralph Excel，您需要做的是
right so if you want to compute me Ralph Excel what you need to do is sum of
Excel what you need to do is sum of extent - one of the potential the joint
范围-扩展器中关节xn减去1的电位之一，这是您
extent - one of the potential the joint xn minus 1 in extender which is this you
xn minus 1 in extender which is this you remember here that's about potential
记住这里是关于我们告诉我的总和的潜在时间
remember here that's about potential times that summation that we told me
times that summation that we told me starting with xn minus 2 all the way to
从xn减2一直到X-1，这就是alpha附近的消息
starting with xn minus 2 all the way to X - 1 and that's the message near alpha
X - 1 and that's the message near alpha text and minus 1 very easy actually to
文字和减号1非常容易，实际上我看不到任何问题。
text and minus 1 very easy actually to visualize no questions I actually when I
visualize no questions I actually when I look at this right I don't look at the
看看这个权利，我不看方程式，因为完整性方法
look at this right I don't look at the equation because the completeness method
equation because the completeness method it's really the message of can stream
这实际上是可以流式传输的消息，即您知道alpha文本n减1
it's really the message of can stream which is you know alpha text n minus 1
which is you know alpha text n minus 1 times this potential and then extra one
倍这个潜力，然后额外的一个必须被整合出来，因为你的阿尔法
times this potential and then extra one has to be integrated out because u alpha
has to be integrated out because u alpha is a function of X N and that's it okay
是XN的功能，就可以了，如果您想给我发消息，也可以
is a function of X N and that's it okay and similarly if you want the message me
and similarly if you want the message me with a recursive relation with Excel
与Excel的递归关系将是从
with a recursive relation with Excel would be the message coming out from the
would be the message coming out from the rival function of xn plus 1 times the
xn的竞争函数加xn的势乘以xn xn的势加1，然后我们
rival function of xn plus 1 times the potential of xn xn plus 1 and then we
potential of xn xn plus 1 and then we integrate out xn plus 1 and that's the
积分出xn加1，这就是这张图中的递归关系
integrate out xn plus 1 and that's the recursive relation okay in this chart
recursive relation okay in this chart the chapman-kolmogorov relations that
查普曼-柯尔莫哥洛夫的关系不仅出现在
the chapman-kolmogorov relations that sort of appear not only the context of
sort of appear not only the context of belief propagation but you know many
信念传播，但对于那些谁
belief propagation but you know many other areas in automatics for those who
other areas in automatics for those who are you know study dynamic programming
您知道研究动态规划这类不合标准的方程式吗？
are you know study dynamic programming sort of the substandard equations we
sort of the substandard equations we look over at dynamic programming
看一下动态编程问题
look over at dynamic programming problems
有人陪我奥斯卡·温特（Oscar Winter）递归之一
someone with me Oscar winter stack one of this recursive
winter stack one of this recursive relation requires for example two no
关系需要例如在边缘没有两个消息，所以我该怎么办
relation requires for example two no messages at the edges so how do I
messages at the edges so how do I calculate the message that x1 Stanwix to
计算我预测的x1 Stanwix给您的消息-所以这里的想法是
calculate the message that x1 Stanwix to you I'll predict - so the idea here is
you I'll predict - so the idea here is the only thing you left is the potential
您唯一剩下的就是潜在的台湾-之前没有
the only thing you left is the potential Taiwan - right there's no previous
Taiwan - right there's no previous message arriving unknown 1 and then what
消息到达未知1，然后您需要做的是在x1上集成
message arriving unknown 1 and then what you need to do is to integrate on x1 and
you need to do is to integrate on x1 and similarly if you want to find the
同样，如果您想找到有关X大写实例的课程
similarly if you want to find the lessons about X capital instance
lessons about X capital instance basically you have to integrate X
基本上，您必须从xn的潜在Phi积分X资本n
basically you have to integrate X capital n from the potential Phi of xn
capital n from the potential Phi of xn plus 1 X sorry X n minus 1 extent okay
加1 X对不起X n减1程度还可以，所以同样地听消失的声音
plus 1 X sorry X n minus 1 extent okay so similarly listening to what disappear
so similarly listening to what disappear so this is sort of abandoned condition
因此，这是一种被遗弃的条件，而另一种边界条件是
so this is sort of abandoned condition and another boundary condition for the
and another boundary condition for the North extent and then recursively you
北范围，然后递归计算所有消息
North extent and then recursively you compute all the messages you compute all
compute all the messages you compute all the messages then you have everything
消息之后，您便拥有了所有可以做的所有边际
the messages then you have everything you have all the marginals you can do
you have all the marginals you can do anything you want all the information is
您想要的所有信息是
在消息内部，所以想想这条消息是对的，如果您知道其中的一些
you have all the marginals you can do anything you want all the information is
is inside of messages so think of this message it's right you know if some of
在消息内部，所以想想这条消息是对的，如果您知道其中的一些
message it's right you know if some of these notes for example of evidence
这些注释，例如证据注释
these notes for example of evidence notes
notes it's basically information that
从这些证据知识中传播出来的基本上是信息
it's basically information that propagates from this evidence knowledge
propagates from this evidence knowledge to the query note that this case is X 10
到查询注意，这种情况是X 10正常，以某种方式有趣的是
to the query note that this case is X 10 ok and somehow what is interesting ok
ok and somehow what is interesting ok and you may want to think this way the
您可能想这样思考，它的注释的边缘是此进度
and you may want to think this way the marginal of its note is is this progress
marginal of its note is is this progress of the messages were coming right from
的消息是从左向右传来的，并以某种方式定义了
of the messages were coming right from the left and arrived define somehow what
the left and arrived define somehow what the status of node X 10 is okay
节点X 10的状态还可以，因此您可以有效地相信
the status of node X 10 is okay so effectively you have belief
so effectively you have belief propagation if you like from x1 to xn
从x1传播到xn并从X大写中和
propagation if you like from x1 to xn and the neutralization of from X capital
and the neutralization of from X capital and physical extent and those two
和物理范围，这两个信息定义了北欧的阶段
and physical extent and those two messages define the stage of the Nordic
messages define the stage of the Nordic sent and it's Martin right you can do
发送，这是马丁，对，您实际上可以进行很多琐碎的计算
sent and it's Martin right you can do actually lots of trivial calculations
actually lots of trivial calculations and give them as to make an e-commerce
并给他们一个电子商务清单。亚诺
and give them as to make an e-commerce to list mr. Arno
to list mr. Arno all right start writing but they put the
好的开始写作，但是他们把下一个沉着的作品放好了
all right start writing but they put the next one massive calm works alright okay
next one massive calm works alright okay so here is the previa calculation and
所以这是previa的计算，假设有人告诉我，让我回去
so here is the previa calculation and let me go back suppose somebody tells
let me go back suppose somebody tells you I want to find the joint probability
你我想找到任意两个任意否的联合概率分布
you I want to find the joint probability distribution of any two arbitrary no I
distribution of any two arbitrary no I mean so don't look at the questions not
意思是，所以不要看问题，不要看笔记，前提是你
mean so don't look at the questions not look at the notes right the suppose you
look at the notes right the suppose you know I'll give you two nodes and I say
知道我会给你两个节点，我说找到我的联合分配是做什么的
know I'll give you two nodes and I say find me the Joint Distribution what did
find me the Joint Distribution what did you do
你是我的意思，你怎么知道只是想
you do I mean how you know just thinking of
I mean how you know just thinking of these messages that define the state
这些消息定义了我拥有联合的状态，您如何看待
these messages that define the state that I have the joint what do you think
that I have the joint what do you think is gonna be happening
将会发生
您可以将音符彼此隔开很远
that I have the joint what do you think is gonna be happening
you can take the notes to be next to each other far away it doesn't really
您可以将音符彼此隔开很远
each other far away it doesn't really matter but if you want the joint of two
无关紧要，但是如果您想将两个音符合并在一起，您认为它将是什么
matter but if you want the joint of two notes what do you think it's going to be
notes what do you think it's going to be the actual result
实际结果
因此，在这种情况下，他们卖给您的价格是xn减去1的总和
notes what do you think it's going to be the actual result
so in this case where they sell to you is the joint of xn minus 1 an extern
因此，在这种情况下，他们卖给您的价格是xn减去1的总和
is the joint of xn minus 1 an extern okay so is the nest is coming from the
好吧，那巢是从左边到xn减1的，那乱七八糟的来了
okay so is the nest is coming from the left to xn minus 1 the mess is coming on
left to xn minus 1 the mess is coming on the right times the potential between
正确乘以6到1之间的电势实际上是一个例子
the right times the potential between the no 6 and minus 1 an example actually
the no 6 and minus 1 an example actually if you don't believe me that this comes
如果您不相信我说的对，那么您需要做的就是开始
if you don't believe me that this comes in right what you need to do is start
in right what you need to do is start with your elimination eliminate all the
消除时消除xn左侧的所有鼻子减去1消除
with your elimination eliminate all the nose to the left of xn minus 1 eliminate
nose to the left of xn minus 1 eliminate all the nose to the right of xn and what
xn右边的所有鼻子，以及第一个先得到的东西，您将得到
all the nose to the right of xn and what you get the first first you will get the
you get the first first you will get the only thing you will not eliminate is the
唯一不会消除的是xn减去1到xn全部之间的电势
only thing you will not eliminate is the potential between xn minus 1 and xn all
potential between xn minus 1 and xn all right
右边左边的总和会给你
right the summation on the left will give you
the summation on the left will give you this mess with the rest of the right
这与其他权利的混乱将给你，并且有
this mess with the rest of the right will give you that and there is the
will give you that and there is the answer okay and you can do this you know
回答好吧，您可以执行此操作，如果您对这些事情做出了很多回应，就知道了
answer okay and you can do this you know if you do lots of response the things
if you do lots of response the things that you want to compute join these
您要计算加入这些条件的信息
that you want to compute join these conditions the information is encoded on
conditions the information is encoded on these messages via nice everything is
这些消息很不错，一旦您将所有信息都编码在此消息上
these messages via nice everything is encoded on this message this once you
encoded on this message this once you have these messages
如果可以的话，无论您有什么疑问，都可以得到这些消息
have these messages whatever query you have if you can
whatever query you have if you can resolve it so the calculation by the way
解决它，以便在变量可以通过所有方式进行计算的情况下
resolve it so the calculation by the way to do all of this if it's variable can
to do all of this if it's variable can take M values in heaven and you know
在天堂取M值，就知道环境
take M values in heaven and you know environments so
这次是两次，因为您必须计算与遇到麻烦
is two times this times because you have to calculate versus coming the trouble
to calculate versus coming the trouble messages and then the backward messages
消息，然后向后的消息计算每个
messages and then the backward messages the calculation of this each of the
the calculation of this each of the messages is basically M square in heaven
消息基本上是天堂中的M平方，也是nm平方，所以成本是两倍
messages is basically M square in heaven also nm square so the cost is two times
also nm square so the cost is two times and M Square and the important thing
和M Square，这里重要的是n是线性的，这就是
and M Square and the important thing here is linear in n and this is what
here is linear in n and this is what you're interested okay
你有兴趣没事
与此算法产品有关的任何变更问题显然都可以
here is linear in n and this is what you're interested okay
any questions with this algorithm product for change obviously you can
与此算法产品有关的任何变更问题显然都可以
product for change obviously you can imagine that this can be generalized to
想象一下，可以将其推广到正确的树上，所以我们将看到它是如何工作的
imagine that this can be generalized to trees right so we will see how it works
trees right so we will see how it works with this little bit it's not tricky yes
这一点并不棘手，是的，同一个想法更少，而且记法
with this little bit it's not tricky yes the same idea more less and the notation
the same idea more less and the notation is the same but you know changed is they
是一样的，但您知道改变了，他们只是等着看发生了什么，所以现在
is the same but you know changed is they just wait to see what's going on so now
just wait to see what's going on so now if we have evidence right how do you
如果我们有正确的证据，您如何明确说明证据？
if we have evidence right how do you account explicitly for the evidence and
account explicitly for the evidence and the answer to our question it it's
我们问题的答案，实际上与我们拥有的方法相同
the answer to our question it it's actually the same way as what we have
actually the same way as what we have done is the so in this case that a you
在这种情况下，您想要计算的不是边际效应
done is the so in this case that a you want to compute not the marginal effects
want to compute not the marginal effects 10 but let's say the conditional of
10，但假设条件的条件是给定X大写X，所以说
10 but let's say the conditional of extent given X capital X so let's say
extent given X capital X so let's say our evidence is X capital F ok so the
我们的证据是X大写F ok，所以您唯一要做的修改是
our evidence is X capital F ok so the only modification you have to do is if
only modification you have to do is if you like is in the boundary condition of
您喜欢处于关于X大写n含义的消息的边界条件
you like is in the boundary condition of the message about X capital n sense to
the message about X capital n sense to extend capital L minus 1 which is this
扩展大写字母L减1，这就是我们所说的潜在可能性之前的消息
extend capital L minus 1 which is this message before we said is the potential
message before we said is the potential of xn minus 1 X 10 you remember the
xn减1 X 10的结果，您还记得边界条件，而不是这个
of xn minus 1 X 10 you remember the boundary condition instead of this what
boundary condition instead of this what we have is with a summation over all
我们拥有的是X资本L的所有可能值的总和
we have is with a summation over all possible values of X capital L now
possible values of X capital L now there's no summation of X capital n we
没有X资本n的总和，我们将X资本n固定为任何值
there's no summation of X capital n we fixed X capital n to whatever value we
fixed X capital n to whatever value we have digital okay so the only change in
数字化还可以，所以算法的唯一变化是而不是求和
have digital okay so the only change in the algorithm is instead of summing over
the algorithm is instead of summing over the values of x capital n all right you
知道x大写n的值就可以了，将x大写n固定为指定的
the values of x capital n all right you know fixing X capital n to a specified
know fixing X capital n to a specified value
值，我的意思是为什么实际上你能做的就是你
value I mean why actually you can do is you
I mean why actually you can do is you can put remember our evidence potential
可以记住我们的证据潜力，您可以在其中添加增量函数，
can put remember our evidence potential there you can put a delta function and
there you can put a delta function and then the channel X capital n but the
那么通道X的大写字母n是唯一值，因为Delta函数
then the channel X capital n but the only value because of the Delta function
only value because of the Delta function will give you will give out and that is
会给你，会给你，那是相同的想法
will give you will give out and that is sort of the same idea
sort of the same idea ok so you the calculations of the
好吧，所以你给这个证据的条件的计算
ok so you the calculations of the conditional to given this evidence
conditional to given this evidence suggest be the same thing as from the
建议和蒙蒂一样
suggest be the same thing as from the Monty
Monty zero change in the algorithm message
算法消息中的零变化来自左侧和右侧
zero change in the algorithm message come from the left and right the only
come from the left and right the only difference is that in the message
不同的是，在从证据中传播出来的信息中，您
difference is that in the message propagating from the evidence here you
propagating from the evidence here you have to change some of the boundary
必须改变一些边界条件，我不是
have to change some of the boundary condition with this all right I am NOT
condition with this all right I am NOT going to do this today
今天要去做，但是我要你去
going to do this today all right but I want you to we're going
all right but I want you to we're going to spent actually a collection on this
实际花了这个算法的一个集合，但我想让你看到你知道
to spent actually a collection on this algorithm but I want you to see you know
algorithm but I want you to see you know everything on you can actually instead
实际上，您可以进行的所有操作都无需进行求和和计算
everything on you can actually instead of doing the summation and computing
of doing the summation and computing marginals somebody will tell you in this
边缘人会告诉你这个链条，你能找到我们的模范吗？
marginals somebody will tell you in this chain can you find us the mold of the
chain can you find us the mold of the Joint Distribution in other ways can you
用其他方式的联合分配可以找到最大的x标记是多少
Joint Distribution in other ways can you find what is the x marks that maximizes
find what is the x marks that maximizes the Joint Distribution is very
联合分配是非常高维非常重要的问题
the Joint Distribution is very high-dimensional very important problem
high-dimensional very important problem but I give all this volume is defined on
但我给所有这些量都在链上定义了，你想找到模式
but I give all this volume is defined on the chain and you want to find the mode
the chain and you want to find the mode of the Joint Distribution
的联合分布，所以在我们求和之前
of the Joint Distribution so before we have the summation alright
so before we have the summation alright and you know and so for example in the
并且您知道，例如在消除算法的上下文中
and you know and so for example in the context of the elimination algorithm
context of the elimination algorithm right rather than coming all the
正确的做法，而不是按照我们的方式来处理所有不同的变量
right rather than coming all the different variables the way we have it
different variables the way we have it now what we need to do is take the
现在我们需要做的是将Tori分解并推动所有
now what we need to do is take the factorization of the Tori and push all
factorization of the Tori and push all the maximizations first on X capital n
首先在X大写n上最大化，然后在xn减去1的过程中一直标记
the maximizations first on X capital n then xn minus 1 all the way to mark
then xn minus 1 all the way to mark small X term so we need to find an
X小项，因此我们需要找到一种有效的算法来执行此操作
small X term so we need to find an efficient algorithm for doing this
efficient algorithm for doing this circle by doing calculations forwards
通过向前和向后进行计算来圈出，这将导致
circle by doing calculations forwards and backwards and that will lead to a
and backwards and that will lead to a very famous dynamic programming
非常著名的动态编程算法，就是您告诉
very famous dynamic programming algorithm which is that you tell the
algorithm which is that you tell the algorithm
好的算法，所以我们将为隐藏执行此操作
algorithm ok and so we will do this for hidden
ok and so we will do this for hidden markov models will spend one lecture
马可夫模型将在一场演讲中使用权利，但我希望您能以某种方式看到它
markov models will spend one lecture right but I want you to see that somehow
right but I want you to see that somehow destination can be replaced with
目的地可以替换为最大化算法
destination can be replaced with maximization the algorithm is sort of
maximization the algorithm is sort of the same but there is some details that
一样，但有一些细节，它们是独特的曲折
the same but there is some details that they are unique twists
they are unique twists Bianca and they are unique because you
比安卡（Bianca）和它们很独特，因为您知道水分过多
Bianca and they are unique because you know you have too much moisture the
know you have too much moisture the joint not the mass goes all right and
联合不是群众顺利，而你这样做的方式介绍了一些
joint not the mass goes all right and the way you do this introduce some
the way you do this introduce some little treat the someone needs to
有人需要在一天结束时考虑一点点的治疗，所以他的
little treat the someone needs to consider at the end of the day so his
consider at the end of the day so his tongue were even worse under much
在很多产品而不是我们将要使用的某些产品下，舌头甚至更糟
tongue were even worse under much product rather than some product we will
product rather than some product we will revisit okay
重新访问还可以
所以我们刚才讨论的求和算法可以
product rather than some product we will revisit okay
so the sum-product algorithm that we just discussed for change you can
所以我们刚才讨论的求和算法可以
just discussed for change you can compute a whole homogenous for trees all
计算出树木的整体同质性，我将再次向您展示
compute a whole homogenous for trees all right and I'm gonna show you again
right and I'm gonna show you again pictures all right
图片可以正确显示我们的无向图，所以它们都是
pictures all right our undirected graph and so they are all
our undirected graph and so they are all directed graphs leading to twist vision
有向图导致扭曲视觉，当我们与
directed graphs leading to twist vision you know you never when we worked with
you know you never when we worked with directed graphs we have some you know
有向图，即使在消除算法中，我们也有一些您知道的
directed graphs we have some you know even in the elimination algorithm to
even in the elimination algorithm to make them undirected so when you we make
使它们无方向性，所以当您直接使它们闭合时，我们总是得到三个
make them undirected so when you we make them on directly do we always get three
them on directly do we always get three so what do we need to get a tree in
所以我们需要什么来指导工作
so what do we need to get a tree in directing job
如果宣布，这与生活中的道德事件有关
it's something to do with the moral events in life if announce that to
events in life if announce that to parents and we transform this sort of
父母，我们直接转换这种图来说明发生了什么事
parents and we transform this sort of directly graph what was happening we
directly graph what was happening we will get what temp and no one with two
会得到什么样的温度，没有人拥有两种力量使变革变得光明
will get what temp and no one with two powers brightening transformational
powers brightening transformational directive what do you get
指令你得到什么
如果您使他们摆脱了道德化的影响，那么您会发现它不是
powers brightening transformational directive what do you get
if you get them out of the moralization effect you get a look so it's not a
如果您使他们摆脱了道德化的影响，那么您会发现它不是
effect you get a look so it's not a three anymore alright but if the if
三个都可以了，但是如果有向图中的所有知识
three anymore alright but if the if every knowledge in the directed graph
every knowledge in the directed graph just one pallet then we do actually get
只是一个货盘，那么如果确实有一个货盘，我们现在确实可以得到三个货盘了
just one pallet then we do actually get the three okay now if in the case of a
the three okay now if in the case of a directed graph that a node would say has
一个节点会说有两个父母要结婚的有向图，你会得到一个
directed graph that a node would say has two parents that you marry and you get a
two parents that you marry and you get a loop right you can actually transform
向右循环，您实际上可以将引导爱指向所谓的点
loop right you can actually transform dot on directing love to what is called
dot on directing love to what is called a poly-tree
一棵多树，它是由
a poly-tree and it comes out using the sponsor of
and it comes out using the sponsor of the fact of graphs that are left behind
我以前的演讲中遗留下来的图表事实，如果您
the fact of graphs that are left behind from my previous lecture you can if you
from my previous lecture you can if you transform than the undirected graph to
比无向图转换成所谓的因子图，然后我们做
transform than the undirected graph to what is called a factor graph then we do
what is called a factor graph then we do get at three my point here is that the
我的观点在这里是三点，即该算法可以处理所有
get at three my point here is that the sample that algorithm can handle all of
sample that algorithm can handle all of these things with the same complexity
这些具有相同复杂性的东西都可以，所以我们学习如何做
these things with the same complexity all right so we learning on how to do
all right so we learning on how to do inference message-passing with trish is
使用trish进行推理消息传递非常重要，因为它适用于
inference message-passing with trish is very important because it's applied to
very important because it's applied to both directed and undirected graphs and
包括有向图和无向图，我们正在讨论这些事情
both directed and undirected graphs and we are serving the things to discuss
we are serving the things to discuss today with pictures okay so this is this
今天有图片还可以，所以这是一个无方向性的三个都可以。
today with pictures okay so this is this is an undirected three okay here every
is an undirected three okay here every node has one part so you know this is
节点只有一部分，所以您知道这是直接输入的内容，如果有
node has one part so you know this is this to the direct entry and if there's
this to the direct entry and if there's no modernization so it needs to
没有现代化，所以它需要类似的东西
no modernization so it needs to something like that okay
something like that okay the only thing that i emphasized here in
我在这里用蓝色强调的唯一的事情就是你在导演中知道的
the only thing that i emphasized here in blue is here you know in the directed
blue is here you know in the directed love to work with conditional
如果我们开始潜能，我喜欢与条件分布一起工作
love to work with conditional distributions if we start the potentials
distributions if we start the potentials their conditional distributions of not
他们没有给出其父级的条件分布和这些分布
their conditional distributions of not given its parent and these distributions
given its parent and these distributions are normalized but when you work in
归一化，但是当您在无定向的情况下工作时
are normalized but when you work in undirected
undirected twist all right the there is a
好吧，通常会有一个归一化的因子，所以
twist all right the there is a normalization factor in general okay so
normalization factor in general okay so in general is a normalization factor
通常，即使在这种情况下，也是一个归一化因子
in general is a normalization factor even in this case if you have some
even in this case if you have some evidence and you can solve this sort of
证据，您可以在那里解决这种定向树
evidence and you can solve this sort of directed tree there
directed tree there very speed of normalization factor the
归一化因子的速度非常快我们基本上有证据的因子
very speed of normalization factor the factor we have an evidence basically
factor we have an evidence basically introduced normalization factor so
引入归一化因子
好吧，这就是43的情况，所以这个家伙有两名飞行员，所以如果你
factor we have an evidence basically introduced normalization factor so
alright then here is the case of the 43 so this guy has two pilots so if you
好吧，这就是43的情况，所以这个家伙有两名飞行员，所以如果你
so this guy has two pilots so if you marry them if you connect them together
如果将它们连接在一起，则将它们嫁给您，就可以创建一个循环，所以这就是
marry them if you connect them together you create a loop right so this is the
you create a loop right so this is the 43 so we will learn I think on the
43所以我们会在明天的讲座上学习我的想法，所以我不会忘记我们
43 so we will learn I think on the lecture tomorrow so I don't forget we're
lecture tomorrow so I don't forget we're going to have election tomorrow we're
明天将要举行选举我们今天将扩展想法，以了解
going to have election tomorrow we're going to extend the ideas today to see
going to extend the ideas today to see how we're going to do influenced only 43
我们怎么做只会影响使用照片的43个人，所以我们要
how we're going to do influenced only 43 using photographs okay so we're going to
using photographs okay so we're going to talk about these misters passing two
谈论这些先生通过两棵非常普通的树好吧，我要
talk about these misters passing two very general trees okay and I'm going to
very general trees okay and I'm going to work with what directed and undirected
使用有向图和无向图，因此我需要提醒您一些
work with what directed and undirected graphs so I need to remind you some of
graphs so I need to remind you some of the notation so let's the work for
记号，所以让我们进行无向风险的工作，以及我在这里所拥有的
the notation so let's the work for undirected risk and what I have here
undirected risk and what I have here this is the tree and I have potential
这是一棵树，我对每个节点都有潜力，我有两对
this is the tree and I have potential for every node and I have two pair
for every node and I have two pair potentials
电位现在可以将每个节点的电位
example right this cell potentials you don't you know in general you don't need
想起它们来证明潜力，例如，正确地利用这个细胞的潜力
您是否不知道您一般不需要它们，因为这里的点击是什么
example right this cell potentials you don't you know in general you don't need
don't you know in general you don't need them because the clicks here what's the
您是否不知道您一般不需要它们，因为这里的点击是什么
them because the clicks here what's the maximum size of the clicks here - okay
此处的最大点击次数-好的，但是您知道您是否无法正确思考
maximum size of the clicks here - okay but you know if you can't think right
but you know if you can't think right but this somehow was was derived by a
但这是通过有向图得出的，那么您将获得
but this somehow was was derived by a directed graph then you will have the
directed graph then you will have the probability of the nodes and those will
节点的概率以及那些将对应于该自身潜力的概率，或者
probability of the nodes and those will correspond to this self potential or if
correspond to this self potential or if you can imagine if one node is
您可以想象如果指定了一个节点，这将是证据
you can imagine if one node is prescribed this would be the evidence
prescribed this would be the evidence potential so it's always good in
潜力，所以除了这对潜力之外，它总是很好的，但是我们
potential so it's always good in addition to this pair potentials but we
addition to this pair potentials but we have for the tree to plug in also itself
必须插入树本身也参加任何不行的事情，所以在
have for the tree to plug in also itself attends just whatever no okay so in an
attends just whatever no okay so in an undirected tree this is the general
无向树，这是一般表达，好吧，这不是
undirected tree this is the general expression okay this is not an
expression okay this is not an approximation
最大派系的近似值，您的潜力或
approximation of the maximal cliques your potential or
of the maximal cliques your potential or you note and dissolution protections now
您现在要注意和解散保护，如果这是直接输入的话
you note and dissolution protections now if this was the direct entry
if this was the direct entry things are a little bit easier because
事情要容易一些，因为在直接输入中，您要做的是
things are a little bit easier because in the direct entry what you do is you
in the direct entry what you do is you start with the probability of the root
从根节点的概率开始，然后就有概率
start with the probability of the root node and then you have the probability
node and then you have the probability of the notes given the product okay
如果您想直接购买产品，可以非常积极地给产品上的笔记
of the notes given the product okay so actively if you want to take a direct
so actively if you want to take a direct entry and transform into an undirected
进入并转换为无向，您可以看到一对一
entry and transform into an undirected you can see the one-to-one
you can see the one-to-one correspondence between this
该对电位中的这些概率之间的对应关系
correspondence between this probabilities in this pair potentials
probabilities in this pair potentials and easily you can make this to
轻松地使它与您知道的方式相对应
and easily you can make this to correspond to that how is that you know
correspond to that how is that you know you can say at the node are make this
您可以在节点上说，让此潜在的皮划艇为X的P感到抱歉
you can say at the node are make this potential kayak sorry for the P of X
potential kayak sorry for the P of X star and make all the other potential
恒星并使所有其他势均等于一个好，所以基本上
star and make all the other potential equal to one okay so so basically this
equal to one okay so so basically this is a very general expression for both
是针对有向和无向富人的非常笼统的表达方式
is a very general expression for both directed and undirected rich
证明我们基本上可以做的另一件事，就是说
evidence we basically the other thing you have to do if let's say the value of
you have to do if let's say the value of x is fixed at X I bar you need to change
x固定在XI柱上，您需要更改阶跃电位的定义
x is fixed at X I bar you need to change the definition of the step potentials
the definition of the step potentials and so the note is not evidence now this
因此，该注释现在无法证明这一潜力就是您从
and so the note is not evidence now this potential is what you started with in
potential is what you started with in evidence no if you just have to plug in
没有证据表明，如果您只需要插入基本上说
evidence no if you just have to plug in this Delta function that basically says
this Delta function that basically says the value of this X I you will get a
XI的值，您将获得一个非零贡献，其中X等于
the value of this X I you will get a nonzero contribution where X is equal to
nonzero contribution where X is equal to X I bar so if you have evidence the
XI条，因此，如果您有证据证明以前的方程式是
X I bar so if you have evidence the previous equation that they had this is
previous equation that they had this is you know the joint now if I want to
如果我想写给定的x的概率，你现在知道关节
you know the joint now if I want to write the probability of x given the
write the probability of x given the evidence the expression is the same this
证明表达是相同的，这是每个节点的自电位
evidence the expression is the same this are the self potentials for each node
are the self potentials for each node but there are the evidence potentials
但是有证据表明这种潜力成倍增长，但是什么是
but there are the evidence potentials this multiplied potential but what is
this multiplied potential but what is important note is when you have evidence
重要说明是，当您有证据证明现在的归一化因子可能不是
important note is when you have evidence the normalization factor now may not be
the normalization factor now may not be one so even if this graph was derived
即使此图是从有向图导出的，
one so even if this graph was derived from the directed graph where everything
from the directed graph where everything is normalized so you notice in this case
已标准化，因此在这种情况下，当我们谈论引用此内容的参考时，您会注意到
is normalized so you notice in this case when we talk about the ref to trace this
when we talk about the ref to trace this are normalized probability is equal to 1
归一化的概率等于1，但是当您有证据表明
are normalized probability is equal to 1 but when you have evidence the
but when you have evidence the normalization factor is not one so in
归一化因子不是一个，因此在某些情况下有证据证明它不是归一化因子
normalization factor is not one so in some cases in problems with evidence it
some cases in problems with evidence it doesn't really matter it kept directed
保持定向或不定向并不重要，因为
doesn't really matter it kept directed or undirected because the degree of
or undirected because the degree of complexity is the same just remember
复杂度是相同的，只是请记住，该归一化因子不是
complexity is the same just remember that this normalization factor is not
that this normalization factor is not one okay
一个还可以
[鼓掌]不需要这个
that this normalization factor is not one okay
[Applause] don't need this
我们不需要这一切，所以让我在开始算法之前提醒您
we don't need this all right so let me remind you before I start the algorithm
remind you before I start the algorithm of somewhere so prefer not the synthetic
所以某个地方的人不喜欢合成的东西，而是某种形式上的意义的东西
of somewhere so prefer not the synthetic things but sort of formal sense things
things but sort of formal sense things that usually you don't see when you
通常在对这个目录进行编程时看不到
that usually you don't see when you program this directory
program this directory suppose that the actual potentials right
假设我们的实际潜力来自一棵有向树，
suppose that the actual potentials right we're coming from a directed tree and
we're coming from a directed tree and indirectly created the traditions we
间接创造了我们合作的传统是XJ的可能性
indirectly created the traditions we work with are the probability of XJ
work with are the probability of XJ given its pilot so let's say the part
给定它的飞行员，让我们说这部分是父级，而其三级是
given its pilot so let's say the part here this run parent versus three its
here this run parent versus three its sixth I suppose now we start we have a
第六，我想现在我们开始在这里有一个查询日志，然后开始消除
sixth I suppose now we start we have a query log here and we start eliminating
query log here and we start eliminating node from the bottom except from the
从底部节点开始，除了联盟的新节点之外，如果我
node from the bottom except from the league's new you may have made that if I
league's new you may have made that if I start coming or node XJ serving an 18 X
开始出现或节点XJ服务18 X a，但这等于1右
start coming or node XJ serving an 18 X a but this will come equal to 1 right
a but this will come equal to 1 right six days we are interested here and we
六天，我们在这里感兴趣，我们科学地将它
six days we are interested here and we scientifically the flex a it will
scientifically the flex a it will disappear because it is equal to one
消失，因为它等于一个还可以，所以假设你
disappear because it is equal to one okay alright so in assuming that you
okay alright so in assuming that you have no evidence in this unconditional
在这种无条件的情况下没有证据可以证明您的直觉
have no evidence in this unconditional case you are instincts solve that this
case you are instincts solve that this note that there is no evidence basically
请注意，基本上没有证据可以在达到之前消除它们
note that there is no evidence basically you can eliminate them before you reach
you can eliminate them before you reach your query no you know what that means
您的查询不，您不知道这意味着什么，请测试我是否对正在发生的事情感兴趣
your query no you know what that means test if I am interested in what is going
test if I am interested in what is going on here and I have a lot of knowledge
在这里，我有很多知识，不仅不在这里，我还能做什么
on here and I have a lot of knowledge with not only does not here what can I
with not only does not here what can I do to those now if you're interested to
如果您有兴趣找出此节点的可能性，请立即执行
do to those now if you're interested to figure out the probability of this node
figure out the probability of this node in the best together they have a lots of
在最好的情况下，他们下面有很多法律，它们不是证据
in the best together they have a lots of laws below that they are not evidence
laws below that they are not evidence now what can I increase for good was now
现在我可以永久增加什么，现在考虑到这种情况
now what can I increase for good was now considering that this is the case
我们可以证明他们可以摆脱他们，因为他们不会做出贡献
we can prove them we can get rid of them because they will not contribute
because they will not contribute anything and you know what that means
任何事情，你知道这意味着什么，如果我有兴趣的话
anything and you know what that means that is actually if I'm interested in
that is actually if I'm interested in what is going on here and down here at
在这里，在这里和在这里下面的能力按顺序排列是正确的
what is going on here and down here at abilities right in the ordering of
abilities right in the ordering of contamination in the only make sense to
假设叶子具有我所能承受的唯一意义是污染
contamination in the only make sense to assume that the leaves have what I could
assume that the leaves have what I could know here if the nodes are not
在这里知道节点是否未指定不是证据的一部分
know here if the nodes are not unspecified are not part of the evidence
unspecified are not part of the evidence will disappear will be cleaned out so
将消失，将被清除，所以我们唯一需要考虑的是
will disappear will be cleaned out so the only thing we need to consider is
the only thing we need to consider is when we know the leaves are what what I
当我们知道叶子是什么我还不明显好吗，所以我们只需要
when we know the leaves are what what I was not evident okay so we only have to
was not evident okay so we only have to consider the case where the the lists
考虑在这种情况下列表基本上是可以的情况
consider the case where the the lists are basically evidence okay in that case
are basically evidence okay in that case remember that normalizations g that we
请记住，我们认为它不希望等于的归一化g
remember that normalizations g that we consider it don't want to be equal to
consider it don't want to be equal to one so we can prove any subtree that
这样一来，我们就可以证明任何子树，争用开发者不是
one so we can prove any subtree that contention developers that are not
contention developers that are not conditioned on by eliminating backwards
以消除向后的情况为条件，所以现在让我们看看会发生什么
conditioned on by eliminating backwards okay so so let's see now what happens
okay so so let's see now what happens okay
好吧，在这种情况下，我声称如果
okay in a case like this I am claiming if
in a case like this I am claiming if this is my evidence node but somehow
这是我的证据节点，但是以某种方式追溯到我可以证明他们，我可以
this is my evidence node but somehow this traced I can prove them and I can
this traced I can prove them and I can do inference on incident support Li so I
对事件支持李进行推断，所以我想让你告诉我为什么它不是
do inference on incident support Li so I want you to tell me why it's not the
want you to tell me why it's not the case
案件
您不必阅读那里的内容，因为我没有时间
want you to tell me why it's not the case
you don't have to read what it says there because I don't have time for
您不必阅读那里的内容，因为我没有时间
there because I don't have time for reading right so just this is my only
阅读正确，所以这只是我唯一的证据，在这里我并不是在暗示
reading right so just this is my only evidence right here I'm not implying
evidence right here I'm not implying that you're not going to account for the
说您不会考虑这些变化，那么说一下潜力，因为
that you're not going to account for the changes let's say the potentials because
changes let's say the potentials because of the evidence but why I can actually
的证据，但为什么我实际上可以将其分为三个可追溯的工作
of the evidence but why I can actually separate this to three traced work in
separate this to three traced work in doing front separately what is they are
分别做前面，这是什么基本图，该图使我能够
doing front separately what is they are fundamental this graph that allows me to
fundamental this graph that allows me to do that
去做
例如，在这里有这些明显的证据，您能告诉我什么
fundamental this graph that allows me to do that
for example with this evident evidence here what can you tell me on the
例如，在这里有这些明显的证据，您能告诉我什么
here what can you tell me on the probability of this note conditioned on
此便笺的概率取决于列表
probability of this note conditioned on on the list
on the list I mean conditioned on the app noticed
我的意思是说，以应用程序为条件的情况下，您能告诉我有关关节的哪些信息
I mean conditioned on the app noticed what can you tell me about the joint
what can you tell me about the joint probability let's say of this and this
让我们说这和它们独立的条件的概率
probability let's say of this and this condition of that they are independent
condition of that they are independent okay so effectively the only thing we
好吧，如此有效，我们真正需要考虑的唯一事情就是
okay so effectively the only thing we really have to consider is anything that
really have to consider is anything that we have observed right you prune it away
我们观察到您将其修剪掉了，唯一的注意是
we have observed right you prune it away all right and the only notes that you're
all right and the only notes that you're going to have to believe we have to be
将不得不相信我们必须是证据叶和其他一切
going to have to believe we have to be evidence leaves and everything else
evidence leaves and everything else basically has to be on themselves that
基本上必须要对自己感兴趣，这样才能很好地进行推理
basically has to be on themselves that will be interesting to do inference okay
will be interesting to do inference okay so there is lots of things that I said
所以我在那儿说了很多事情，但其中一些基本上是
so there is lots of things that I said there but some of them basically are
there but some of them basically are sort of common strands coming in the
在此直接草稿的背景下，有种共同点
sort of common strands coming in the context of the direct draft from this
context of the direct draft from this relation there is no point of doing
关系是没有意义的站等于他们的答案
relation there is no point of doing stations that they are equal to answer
stations that they are equal to answer what you need to do is prune leaves that
您需要做的是基本上没有观察到的李子叶，如果有的话
what you need to do is prune leaves that are basically unobserved and if you have
are basically unobserved and if you have evidence you have to be careful to know
证据，您必须要小心知道，因为证据会将图形分开，并且
evidence you have to be careful to know because evidence splits the graph and
because evidence splits the graph and then you may be able to have inference
那么您可能可以在这种情况下通过三种不同的方式进行推断
then you may be able to have inference in like this case with three different
in like this case with three different graphs so we're going to stop doing
图，所以我们将停止传递扭曲消息并进行泛化
graphs so we're going to stop doing message passing on twist and generalize
message passing on twist and generalize the the algorithm we saw on on a chain
我们在链上看到的算法，所以现在将在树上
the the algorithm we saw on on a chain so this now would be on the tree the
so this now would be on the tree the same any are criticized know which the
同样任何受到批评的人都知道一阶消除
same any are criticized know which the first order elimination
我们将不得不采取某种方式消除音符，或者
we're gonna have to do some elimination of the notes right then one way or
of the notes right then one way or another it's a tree I'm going to give
另一个是一棵树，我要给你一个算法，这是今天的演讲
another it's a tree I'm going to give you an algorithm is the lecture today
you an algorithm is the lecture today and that defines first-order but in this
并定义了一阶，但在这种情况下，一阶是您开始
and that defines first-order but in this case the first order is you start
case the first order is you start basically from the left subtree which is
基本上是从左边的子树开始，这是从左边开始
basically from the left subtree which is this and you start from the left to the
this and you start from the left to the right of 4 5 2 3 and 1
4 5 2 3和1 ok的右边，所以显然在每个sub 3中
right of 4 5 2 3 and 1 ok so obviously in every sub 3 you have
ok so obviously in every sub 3 you have to start from the child's but always
从孩子的开始，但总是从左边开始，所以5到3个人都可以
to start from the child's but always from the left so for 5 to 3 anyone ok I
from the left so for 5 to 3 anyone ok I gave here that's gonna stack you want to
给了你要单击它的堆栈，但是我要给你
gave here that's gonna stack you want to click it but I'm going to give you the
click it but I'm going to give you the algorithm and all of this algorithms
算法以及您在Threes上看到的所有这些算法
algorithm and all of this algorithms that you would see on Three's they're
that you would see on Three's they're already cursing so I don't know if you
已经在咒骂，所以我不知道您是否曾经用递归编程
already cursing so I don't know if you ever programmed anything with recursive
ever programmed anything with recursive algorithms but sort of you need to get
算法，但是当您执行某种消息时，您需要习惯
algorithms but sort of you need to get used to when you do sort of message
used to when you do sort of message passing algorithm okay so let me we have
通过算法好吧，让我进行一阶消除，我要
passing algorithm okay so let me we have a first order elimination and I'm gonna
a first order elimination and I'm gonna give you a message passing version of
给您一个消除算法的消息传递版本，所以说
give you a message passing version of the elimination algorithm so let's say
the elimination algorithm so let's say let's say that we're interested we have
假设我们很感兴趣，我们有证据证明现在有2和X 4和X 5
let's say that we're interested we have evidence of now such 2 and X 4 and X 5
evidence of now such 2 and X 4 and X 5 right and somebody tells you compute the
正确，有人告诉您计算X 3的条件，所以基本上
right and somebody tells you compute the conditional of X 3 okay so basically
conditional of X 3 okay so basically what we need to do is we need to
我们需要做的是我们需要在这里集成X 1，所以让我们
what we need to do is we need to integrate X 1 here all right so let's
integrate X 1 here all right so let's say the factorization theorist myself
我自己说因式分解理论家，您知道所有的潜力
say the factorization theorist myself you know certain all potentials which
you know certain all potentials which are based at least evidence modify
至少根据证据可以改变耳聋的可能性
are based at least evidence modify deafness potentials be introduced before
deafness potentials be introduced before this playoffs xixj because my colleagues
这个季后赛xixj，因为我的同事的最大人数是2，所以我在写
this playoffs xixj because my colleagues have maximum size is 2 so I am writing
have maximum size is 2 so I am writing least an undirected graph so I have
至少是一个无向图，所以我对谢尔福德·谢尔福德（Salford Xie）的性爱自负
least an undirected graph so I have pretentious for Salford Xie for sexual
pretentious for Salford Xie for sexual onyx to explore its 385 but and I have
玛瑙，以探索其385，但我有潜力6 1 X 2 X 1 X 3 X 3 X 4
onyx to explore its 385 but and I have the potential 6 1 X 2 X 1 X 3 X 3 X 4
the potential 6 1 X 2 X 1 X 3 X 3 X 4 and X 3 X 5 so what I have done here is
和X 3 X 5，所以我在这里所做的是X 2 X 4 X 5，我不需要
and X 3 X 5 so what I have done here is X 2 X 4 X 5 are given right I don't need
X 2 X 4 X 5 are given right I don't need to do any modifications the only
进行任何修改，唯一的修改是在定义内
to do any modifications the only modifications are inside the definition
modifications are inside the definition of this tie a right so there's no need
这个领带的权利，所以不需要用三角洲听起来1 X 2 X 4 X 5
of this tie a right so there's no need to sound 1 X 2 X 4 X 5 with a delta
to sound 1 X 2 X 4 X 5 with a delta function because this is already done
功能，因为这已经在里面完成抱歉，所以我唯一的事情
function because this is already done inside sorry so the only thing I have
inside sorry so the only thing I have here is estimation of next month all
这是下个月的估计，可以估计电子但低于
here is estimation of next month all right estimation electron but below the
right estimation electron but below the summation you see some definitions that
总结一下，您会看到一些定义，我希望您仔细看一下
summation you see some definitions that I want you to look carefully on what is
I want you to look carefully on what is definitions imply in the context of
定义暗示着一次消除一个注释，因此让我们
definitions imply in the context of eliminating Note one at a time so let's
eliminating Note one at a time so let's look at this last term okay so when
看看最后一个学期好吧，所以当您感兴趣时，您会记住条件
look at this last term okay so when interested you remember the conditional
interested you remember the conditional of X 3 given this evidence okay so the
X的X 3给出此证据还可以，所以我看到的最后一项改变了单元格
of X 3 given this evidence okay so the last term I see changed the cell
last term I see changed the cell potential of X 5 right and then the
X 5的潜力，然后我们过期的潜在影响就好了
potential of X 5 right and then the potential effects we are expired okay
现在没有解决方案或过期的原因这里值得再次阀门是
now the reason there is no solution or expired here is worth again valve is the
expired here is worth again valve is the summation of X 5 because turning it okay
X 5的总和，因为可以了，还有另一个函数会尝试
summation of X 5 because turning it okay there is another function that will try
there is another function that will try SEC strive to be expired are there okay
如果您想明确地将SEC声明为过期，SEC会继续努力吗？
SEC strive to be expired are there okay again if you want to put explicitly with
again if you want to put explicitly with a delta function there it will take care
那里有一个delta函数，它会照顾好它，但是你知道吗，所以你可以
a delta function there it will take care of it but you know alright so can you
of it but you know alright so can you tell me just basically what is this
告诉我基本上您认为该产品对我们来说是什么尝试
tell me just basically what is this product you think doing for us is try of
product you think doing for us is try of X 5 times I of X 5 4 X 3 okay I always
X 5乘以X 5 4的X 3 X好吧，我总是真的注意到这一点，并且使用基材5 3
X 5 times I of X 5 4 X 3 okay I always really noted this and with substrate 5 3
really noted this and with substrate 5 3 and it's a function of X 3 because X 5
这是X 3的函数，因为X 5只是成本，所以那是什么
and it's a function of X 3 because X 5 is just the cost so what is that
is just the cost so what is that if we are going to put some words to
如果我们要说几句话来定义它，那么这里的符号是固定的
if we are going to put some words to define it what is that sign here fix
define it what is that sign here fix five times the potential of X 3 X 5 what
X 3 X 5的潜力的五倍是什么？我的意思是，M显然代表
five times the potential of X 3 X 5 what is up I mean obviously M stands for
is up I mean obviously M stands for message so what is that
消息，那是什么
是x5 1033消息吗，这个你知道这是什么吗？
is up I mean obviously M stands for message so what is that
is the message x5 1033 okay and this one you know what this is it is evidence
是x5 1033消息吗，这个你知道这是什么吗？
you know what this is it is evidence propagation from below to know the
从下面传播，以了解极限事实，即xx5具有某些价值
propagation from below to know the extreme the fact that xx5 has some value
extreme the fact that xx5 has some value interesting thing for x3 and other
x3有趣的事情以及此消息中包含的其他含义
interesting thing for x3 and other implications contained from this message
因此，您已经准备就绪，您可以知道信念传播还可以，并且类似地，
so it is ready you know belief propagation okay and similarly the
propagation okay and similarly the second term side effects four times the
第二学期副作用四次经验丰富的四个的关节是这个
second term side effects four times the joint of experienced four is this
joint of experienced four is this message from four to three okay so this
消息从四到三行，所以这是从X 4 X 3传递过来的消息
message from four to three okay so this is message passing from X 4 X 3 so
is message passing from X 4 X 3 so evidence probe x4 propagates to three
证据探测器x4类似地将消息从x3传播到三个x1
evidence probe x4 propagates to three similarly the message from x3 to x1
similarly the message from x3 to x1 which is lit alright so we're rewriting
没关系，所以我们现在要重写此等式
which is lit alright so we're rewriting this equation now this there's no
this equation now this there's no summation X 3 so this goes outside and
总和X 3，因此超出范围，并且x1距离上的安装取决于
summation X 3 so this goes outside and the installation on x1 distance depend
the installation on x1 distance depend only on x2 ratio I don't touch them and
仅按x2的比例，我不触摸它们，并且有目标x1，所以让我们看一下
only on x2 ratio I don't touch them and there is destination x1 so let's look at
there is destination x1 so let's look at this list very carefully it says take
这个清单非常仔细，说要拿证据，所以我们有两个肚子
this list very carefully it says take the evidence on so we have two stomachs
the evidence on so we have two stomachs one ok so take the evidence of node X 1
一个就好，所以取节点X 1的证据好吧取x1 x3的电势
one ok so take the evidence of node X 1 all right take the potential of x1 x3
all right take the potential of x1 x3 and take the message that is propagated
并删除从节点2虚拟传播的消息，然后摆脱
and take the message that is propagated virtual from node 2 and then get rid of
virtual from node 2 and then get rid of X 1 so I wish you'd remember when we
X 1，所以我希望您会记得我们讨论变化时，我们拥有
X 1 so I wish you'd remember when we discuss about change and and we have the
discuss about change and and we have the recasting this form of our relations and
重铸这种形式的我们的关系，并以这种方式产生大师
recasting this form of our relations and result the Masters this way it is the
result the Masters this way it is the potential times the messes coming in and
潜在的时间混乱进入，然后整合先前的变量
potential times the messes coming in and then go integrate the previous variables
then go integrate the previous variables out so look at this it stays here if I
出来看看，如果我把它叫做m13，则遗嘱3留在这里
out so look at this it stays here if I call this m13 the testament 3 is the
call this m13 the testament 3 is the potential of x1 and the potential X 1 X
x1的电势和X 1 X 2的电势乘以来自节点2的混乱
potential of x1 and the potential X 1 X 2 times the mess is coming from node 2
2 times the mess is coming from node 2 and then integrating note you are the
然后整合笔记你实际上是唯一的东西
and then integrating note you are the only thing that is actually
only thing that is actually from what we had before is but now we
从以前的情况来看，但现在我们已经包含了自身的潜在节点
from what we had before is but now we have included itself potential nodes
have included itself potential nodes that need to carry them all right but if
需要让他们一切都好，但是如果您想要任何理由，可以
that need to carry them all right but if whatever reason you wanted you could
whatever reason you wanted you could have integrate those inside aspera
也整合了内部的阿斯佩拉电位，因此方程式将
have integrate those inside aspera potentials as well so the equation would
potentials as well so the equation would look identical but again the recursive
看起来一样，但递归方程式又说她太难找了
look identical but again the recursive equation says she's too tough to find
equation says she's too tough to find them 1/3 which the function of X 3
X 3的功能将电子积分的1/3的电势
them 1/3 which the function of X 3 integrate electron the cell potential of
integrate electron the cell potential of this node the joint potential of X 1 X 2
这个节点的X 1 X 2的联合势能和消息到达X节点
this node the joint potential of X 1 X 2 and the message arrived in a node X bar
and the message arrived in a node X bar so the master sub base can propagate it
因此主子库可以传播它，这是消息传入的时间
so the master sub base can propagate it is the message coming in times these
is the message coming in times these potentials with actual eliminate make
实际消除的电位有点奇怪
potentials with actual eliminate make strange sense a little bit
再说一遍，如果你知道方程式的问题
and again in case you know what if you look at the equation the question of
look at the equation the question of total power looks you know not
总功率看起来并不复杂，但是您知道如果得到
total power looks you know not complicated but you know if you get a
complicated but you know if you get a much better sense if you look at the
如果您看正确的图并说看信息，则感觉更好
much better sense if you look at the graph right and you say look information
graph right and you say look information propagates from the evidence to know x3
从证据传播到知道x3，但是传播它的信息有
propagates from the evidence to know x3 but the information to propagate it has
but the information to propagate it has to first go to node X 1 how does it do
首先转到节点X 1如何使用此消息执行此操作
to first go to node X 1 how does it do this with this message
this with this message M 2 1 okay which is this and then
M 2 1好的，这是必须的，然后信息必须从节点X 1传递到
M 2 1 okay which is this and then information has to go from node X 1 to
information has to go from node X 1 to node X 3 and this is the lastest and 1/3
节点X 3，这是最新节点，而1/3则如何获得它们，否则3取决于
node X 3 and this is the lastest and 1/3 how do you get them or 3 is by
how do you get them or 3 is by eliminating X 1 and how do you eliminate
消除X 1以及如何消除X 1乘以第一个电位
eliminating X 1 and how do you eliminate X 1 you multiply the potential first one
X 1 you multiply the potential first one the joint returns to X 1 X 2 and then
关节返回X 1 X 2，然后出现消息，因为所有消息
the joint returns to X 1 X 2 and then coming message because all the messages
coming message because all the messages from the evidence need to be propagated
从证据需要通过权利传播，所以一起1 3
from the evidence need to be propagated through right and so together 1 3 you
through right and so together 1 3 you have to compute M 2 1 which also implies
必须计算M 2 1，这也意味着消息的这种计算必须
have to compute M 2 1 which also implies that this calculation of messages has to
that this calculation of messages has to be done in the order of elimination of
以消除否的顺序完成，您无法再长出另一个炉ration
be done in the order of elimination of no you cannot grow another Gration
no you cannot grow another Gration calculate M 1 3 before calculating M 2 1
在计算M 2 1之前先计算M 1 3，因为您将没有足够的空间
calculate M 1 3 before calculating M 2 1 because you will not have enough
because you will not have enough information to do the calculation okay
信息可以进行计算，但是我可以告诉消息太晚了
information to do the calculation okay however I can tell too late the message
however I can tell too late the message from X 1 to X 3 at the same time as I
从X 1到X 3同时计算从2到1的消息，所以
from X 1 to X 3 at the same time as I calculate the messages from 2 to 1 so
calculate the messages from 2 to 1 so actually you can do all of this in
实际上，您可以并行执行所有这些操作，但是您基本上需要
actually you can do all of this in parallel right but you need to basically
parallel right but you need to basically have a scheme that says you can only
有一个方案说您只能传播，如果您只能计算
have a scheme that says you can only propagate if you can only calculate the
propagate if you can only calculate the message will not have to know so you can
消息将不必知道，因此您可以传播，比如说来自公路的消息
message will not have to know so you can propagate let's say a message from road
propagate let's say a message from road 1 2 3 all the whole incoming messages to
1 2 3到节点1的所有传入消息已经全部存在
1 2 3 all the whole incoming messages to node 1 are already there
node 1 are already there this is like doing power programming
这就像在进行电源编程一样，然后您说您知道是否
this is like doing power programming right then you say you know if you
right then you say you know if you noticed executing and sending
注意到在所有其他地方执行和发送信息
noticed executing and sending information somewhere else if all the
information somewhere else if all the information
信息船已经到达该信息
ship has arrived in that information here is this incoming messages okay all
这是传入的消息，好的，现在我们的语言是什么
here is this incoming messages okay all right so anything our language now
right so anything our language now practically identical to what we
几乎与我们讨论过的扭曲以及我们所讨论的完全相同
practically identical to what we discussed off twist and what we
discussed off twist and what we described the last five minutes so let
描述了最后五分钟，所以让我定义一下，如果您知道这是全部
described the last five minutes so let me define so if you know here is all of
me define so if you know here is all of us have cell phones actually I don't
我们实际上有手机我不知道为什么他们应该看起来像这样
us have cell phones actually I don't know why they should look here like
know why they should look here like ellipsis but so of this unknown okay so
省略号，但是这个未知的好吧，所以我们说这有点问题
ellipsis but so of this unknown okay so let's say that this is something up
let's say that this is something up there the root node this is no block aye
那里的根节点不是块，这是J，我们要计算
there the root node this is no block aye and this is J and we want to compute the
and this is J and we want to compute the message a sense to know died
消息使人知道死亡，所以消息Jason仍然活着
message a sense to know died so the message Jason still alive again
so the message Jason still alive again don't look at the equations right it
不要看方程式正确，这将是非陪审团的电池潜力
don't look at the equations right it would be the cell potential of non-jury
would be the cell potential of non-jury right the joint potential of
对神经科学的联合潜力a和所有人的乘积
right the joint potential of neuroscience a and the product of all
neuroscience a and the product of all the messages arriving today from all of
今天从所有这些邻居那里收到的消息，除了没有死，都是
the messages arriving today from all of these neighbors except no die so are all
these neighbors except no die so are all the message to the right from below and
从下面向右的消息，然后是gusano J，或者这意味着我们
the message to the right from below and then gusano J or which means we
then gusano J or which means we eliminate a okay so summation J of the
消除一个好，所以求和XJ的细胞电势的J为联合电势
eliminate a okay so summation J of the cell potential of XJ the joint potential
cell potential of XJ the joint potential clients a and all the messages arriving
客户端a和所有消息从其所有节点的下方从节点到达
clients a and all the messages arriving at node J from below from all of its
at node J from below from all of its neighbors except our you're not gonna
邻居，除了我们，您不会忍受不死消息
neighbors except our you're not gonna stand to use to no die a message you
stand to use to no die a message you received a line and actually that's a
收到一行，这实际上是一个非常哲学的陈述，如果
received a line and actually that's a very philosophical statement and if
very philosophical statement and if you're interested can give you
您有兴趣可以给您信息以阅读有关内容，因此
you're interested can give you information to read about it alright so
information to read about it alright so in other ways you know if you don't you
通过其他方式，您知道是否知道自己可能想让自己感觉到
in other ways you know if you don't you know you may like to make yourself feel
know you may like to make yourself feel good and send messages to yourself but
很好，并向自己发送消息，但这实际上是您的问题
good and send messages to yourself but that actually it your problem
that actually it your problem letter problem okay
字母问题好吗
我们不要杀死僵化的人，因为这与领土无关
that actually it your problem letter problem okay
let's not kill ossifies because that's nothing with territory to be okay any
我们不要杀死僵化的人，因为这与领土无关
nothing with territory to be okay any question some of this is actually the
问题，这实际上是爱荷华州吗？你能告诉我这是什么吗？
question some of this is actually the Iowa does can you tell me what's the
Iowa does can you tell me what's the difference of the difference from the
与我们之前看到的链算法的差异之间的差异
difference of the difference from the chain algorithm that we saw before right
chain algorithm that we saw before right just one big chain so look at this and
只是一个大连锁店，所以看看这个，告诉我与以前有什么不同
just one big chain so look at this and tell me what is different from before
tell me what is different from before every single term that looks different
每个看起来都不同的术语
这里有什么不同，例如，在一个链条中，什么是小产品，什么
tell me what is different from before every single term that looks different
what is different here for example in a chain what was it a little product what
这里有什么不同，例如，在一个链条中，什么是小产品，什么
chain what was it a little product what did we have if you have a chain this one
如果您有一条没有北或另一节点的链条，我们怎么办？
did we have if you have a chain this one no the northern or another node so how
no the northern or another node so how many neighbors except I do we have work
许多邻居，除了我，我们为节点a工作，所以这里只有
many neighbors except I do we have work for the nodes a so here there is only
for the nodes a so here there is only one the incoming method alright and what
一种传入的方法好吧，我们没有明确的权利，而您
one the incoming method alright and what we do not have explicitly right and you
we do not have explicitly right and you know again it makes no difference we do
再次知道这没有什么区别，我们没有这一步潜力，那就是
know again it makes no difference we do not have this step potential that is
not have this step potential that is listen to incorporate basically evidence
听取基本上包括证据就可以了，所以这个已经存在了
listen to incorporate basically evidence okay so this was already there this was
okay so this was already there this was only one term and elimination of XJ this
只有一个词和XJ消除这种关系，这是他们的信息
only one term and elimination of XJ this relationship that's the message they
relationship that's the message they send out okay so if you want to compute
发送好吧，所以如果您想计算那么多，这些计算表明
send out okay so if you want to compute so many do these calculations that say
so many do these calculations that say your interest to go on and find the
您有兴趣继续并根据给定的条件找到根节点的条件
your interest to go on and find the conditional of the root node given the
conditional of the root node given the evidence in this case okay so let me
在这种情况下的证据还可以，所以让我，因为我在这里看到了计算结果
evidence in this case okay so let me because I see the calculation here
because I see the calculation here remind me when we wanted to find the
提醒我，当我们想找到边际违法知识时，我们做了什么
remind me when we wanted to find the marginal offending knowledge what did we
marginal offending knowledge what did we do on the chain when we want to find the
当我们想找到任何否的边际时，在链上做
do on the chain when we want to find the marginal of any No
俗话说，你知道有左右两边的知识，所以
the in the saying you know there was left and right to have the knowledge so
left and right to have the knowledge so what do we do
我们该怎么做，我们采取了主人的性格
what do we do we took the Masters character of the
we took the Masters character of the left the mess is coming from the right
左乱七八糟是从右边来的，我们的口味将是任何东西
left the mess is coming from the right in general our taste will be whatever
in general our taste will be whatever the Masters are coming if we multiply we
大师们来了，如果我们相乘，我们就让他们变得微不足道，现在我尝试看看
the Masters are coming if we multiply we get them the marginal now I try to look
get them the marginal now I try to look at the roof no don't leave any messages
在屋顶上，请不要在上面留下任何消息，因此，
at the roof no don't leave any messages coming from above good note so the
coming from above good note so the message is coming from from below so
消息是从下面传来的，所以基本上您所拥有的就是
message is coming from from below so basically what you have is all the
basically what you have is all the message is coming to the root node from
消息显然从下面的时间从其邻居到达根节点
message is coming to the root node from its neighbors from below times obviously
its neighbors from below times obviously I have to put the search potential of
如果根节点不是一个，我必须把根节点的搜索潜力确定为
I have to put the search potential of the root node okay if it is not one and
the root node okay if it is not one and then if you want you to normalize this
然后，如果您希望以共享分母的方式对此进行规范化
then if you want you to normalize this the way you share the denominator
the way you share the denominator obviously this equation will apply to
显然，该方程式适用于任何要查找的节点
obviously this equation will apply to any node which if you want to find the
any node which if you want to find the marginal of no ties you take the
无边际的边缘，您会考虑所有即将来临的消息的结果
marginal of no ties you take the products of all of the messages coming
products of all of the messages coming up now die from below all right and then
现在从下面消失，然后在这里归一化，您可以
up now die from below all right and then just normalize here and you can get the
just normalize here and you can get the conditional of node I given the evidence
有条件的节点我给出了证据，实际上没有，这就是表格
conditional of node I given the evidence and actually no that's the table
and actually no that's the table question okay well say sphere your
问题好吧，请说出您的相似方程来求边际
question okay well say sphere your similar equations to find the marginal
similar equations to find the marginal at every node okay now the bottom line
现在在每个节点上都可以看到最底线，也许就像我们用红色标出的那样
at every node okay now the bottom line and maybe as we have put this with red
and maybe as we have put this with red letters or something coloring there is
字母或一些与此有关的颜色现在称量它呈线性比例
letters or something coloring there is about this now weighs it scales linearly
about this now weighs it scales linearly with the size of of the tree this is
树的大小，这基本上是您可以做的最好的事情
with the size of of the tree this is basically the best you can do all right
basically the best you can do all right dunya cost Rafi okay and all the
dunya花费Rafi好的，所有方程式完全一样，没有，没有
dunya cost Rafi okay and all the equations are exactly as no there's no
equations are exactly as no there's no approximation okay so we need to do
近似好了，所以我们需要做的实际上是我们今天完成的
approximation okay so we need to do actually we finished today doing
actually we finished today doing different examples because they look
不同的例子，因为它们看起来微不足道，现在您应该告诉我
different examples because they look trivial now you should've told me that
trivial now you should've told me that in the homework some of you arrived on
在家庭作业中，你们中的一些人开始做一些计算，
in the homework some of you arrived on doing calculations some calculations by
doing calculations some calculations by can you not living problems some of you
你能不能生活问题，你们中的一些人全都崩溃了吗
can you not living problems some of you were all down
were all down some of this and that should be the
其中一些，这应该是正确的答案，最后一个选项不是
some of this and that should be the answer right the last one option is not
answer right the last one option is not a good one we have tried the lighted by
我们已经尝试过一个很好的方法，由Chen点燃来进行所有计算，或者
a good one we have tried the lighted by Chen to do all the calculations or
Chen to do all the calculations or actually write a computer program to do
实际上写一个计算机程序来做到这一点，但不要说你知道什么
actually write a computer program to do this but don't say what you know what
this but don't say what you know what you multiply first and even your sound
您首先要乘以声音，然后再乘以声音就可以解决问题
you multiply first and even your sound and whatever comes out to be the answer
and whatever comes out to be the answer that doesn't help
如果我理解正确的话那是没有帮助的
that doesn't help right if I understood correctly okay
right if I understood correctly okay something like that so let's take a
像这样的事情，让我们举一个简单的例子，我们对这里感兴趣
something like that so let's take a simple case we are interested here to
simple case we are interested here to complete the marginals in this temple
完成这庙宇树的边缘，所以很明显，我们将拥有
complete the marginals in this temple tree so obviously we're going to have
tree so obviously we're going to have some post positive elimination here and
一些后消极在这里，这个地方将是这个节点和这个
some post positive elimination here and this place will be this node and this
this place will be this node and this and this and that
这个，那好吧，我们要开始发送
and this and that okay so we're gonna start sending
okay so we're gonna start sending messages from the leaves all the way up
消息从叶子一直传到根，这样我就可以将这些消息发送出去
messages from the leaves all the way up to the root so I can send this messes up
to the root so I can send this messes up in this message simultaneously and once
同时在此消息中，一旦知道树已收到这两个
in this message simultaneously and once know the tree has received this two
know the tree has received this two messages then I can send the message to
消息，然后我可以将消息发送到顶部两点，我们应该正确
messages then I can send the message to the top two o'clock we should have right
the top two o'clock we should have right so we didn't do this all up the same
所以我们并没有在同一步骤中完成所有操作，而是向此处发送一条消息
so we didn't do this all up the same step right here send one message to this
step right here send one message to this together then you can send the messages
然后，您可以发送邮件，一旦打开
together then you can send the messages once you have that you can turn the
once you have that you can turn the message to no one once node one has
节点一收到此消息后就没有消息发送给他们
message to no one once node one has received this message then can send them
received this message then can send them a message back you know - all right so
返回一条消息，您知道-好的，所以节点1发送一条消息1 2 2 2和
a message back you know - all right so so node 1 sends a message a 1 2 2 2 and
so node 1 sends a message a 1 2 2 2 and then you are ready to do what now is
那么您就可以开始执行此操作了，现在可以将消息发送给
then you are ready to do what now is this now ready to send the message to
this now ready to send the message to North Korea would be we need to send a
朝鲜是我们需要从2到3发送消息
North Korea would be we need to send a message from 2 to 3
您需要知道所有传入的消息，这就是这个，而这个您
you need to know all the incoming message which is this and this which you
message which is this and this which you calculate it so then you can send the
计算它，然后您就可以将消息从两到三发送给您了
calculate it so then you can send the message to you know from two to three
message to you know from two to three which is this message here and then what
这是这条消息，然后如果需要，我们需要先发送该消息
which is this message here and then what we need to send the message before if
we need to send the message before if you need this and you need that so if
您需要它，并且您需要它，因此，如果您可以将消息发送到第四个
you need this and you need that so if you can send the message to the fourth
you can send the message to the fourth so effectively actually once did you get
如此有效，实际上，一旦收到此消息，您就可以关闭任何
so effectively actually once did you get this message here you can turn off any
this message here you can turn off any stunts all sending messages to walk
阻碍所有发送消息以遍历所有三个消息，不，这是为您而准备的
stunts all sending messages to walk through all three and no it's for as you
through all three and no it's for as you see here okay
这些混乱完成后，您可以在这里看到，您可以
see here okay once these messes are completed you can
once these messes are completed you can go and calculate anything you want the
去计算任何你想要的边际就可以对条件进行归一化
go and calculate anything you want the marginals you can normalize conditionals
marginals you can normalize conditionals you can put evidence you can do anything
您可以证明您现在可以做任何您想做的事情，当您
you can put evidence you can do anything you want okay now obviously when you
you want okay now obviously when you program there is the tricky part is to
程序中有一个棘手的部分是能够计算消息而不仅仅是一个
program there is the tricky part is to be able to compute messages not just one
be able to compute messages not just one after the other but you have some
一个接一个，但是你有一些算法说你知道我能做什么
after the other but you have some algorithm that says you know what I can
algorithm that says you know what I can compute this by simultaneously then once
同时进行计算，一旦您在这里收到所有消息，我就可以
compute this by simultaneously then once you have all this message here I can
you have all this message here I can compute the outgoing message etc etc so
计算外发消息等，所以您需要某种方法来找出
compute the outgoing message etc etc so you need to have some way to figure out
you need to have some way to figure out when a node is ready to send messages to
当一个节点准备好向邻居发送消息时，这两个
when a node is ready to send messages to its neighbors all right is this two
its neighbors all right is this two different different okay so in this
不同，不同，好吧，所以在这张图中您可以看到重要性
different different okay so in this graph you can see the importance
graph you can see the importance actually for having a protocol to send
实际上是因为有协议发送消息通知，但是在这里我可以
actually for having a protocol to send messages notice but here I can
messages notice but here I can simultaneously end this messages that
同时结束您在图B上看到的此消息，没有任何承诺
simultaneously end this messages that you see on a figure B no promises
you see on a figure B no promises promises all at the time and I can do
承诺所有的时间，我可以做到这一点，因为这个节点还可以
promises all at the time and I can do this right because this node all right
this right because this node all right can send the message there all right the
可以在那里发送消息，没问题，这里一样
can send the message there all right the same here same there
same here same there all right so on the second stage I do
好的，所以在第二阶段，我确实注意到带有虚线的消息
all right so on the second stage I do notice messages with dotted lines to
notice messages with dotted lines to indicate that I calculate them
表示我之前已经计算过，但是一旦放置，她就没有了
indicate that I calculate them previously but once placed no she has
previously but once placed no she has received messages from the left and the
从左右两边收到的消息可以执行的操作可以发送
received messages from the left and the right where they can do it can send the
right where they can do it can send the message to this node and once this node
消息发送到此节点，并且一旦此节点在此接收到西密歇根州的
message to this node and once this node here to receive this to West Michigan's
here to receive this to West Michigan's tell the vessels
告诉船只，所以在最后一步，你会注意到我
tell the vessels so on the last step you notice I make
so on the last step you notice I make all these messages about it because they
关于这些消息的所有这些消息，因为它们是在此注释之前（如果有）计算得出的
all these messages about it because they calculated before and if if this note
calculated before and if if this note has a message from below has a message
从下面有一条消息从右边有一条消息，然后可以发送
has a message from below has a message already from the right then it can send
already from the right then it can send a message to this node similarly if this
如果此节点有船只进入，则向该节点发送一条类似的消息
a message to this node similarly if this node has the vessels coming in as a
node has the vessels coming in as a message from the right it can send a
正确的消息可以向该法律发送消息，这样您就永远
message from the right it can send a message to this law okay so you never
message to this law okay so you never idea that what I mean a part of the
我的意思是协议的一部分，基本上是用于发送消息的想法
idea that what I mean a part of the protocol basically for sending messages
protocol basically for sending messages if you do this sequentially obviously is
如果您依次执行此操作，显然不是一个好的算法，并且
if you do this sequentially obviously is not gonna be a good algorithm and
not gonna be a good algorithm and according the graph is going to be
根据图将可能是如果您这样做正确时
according the graph is going to be probably if you do this right when the
probably if you do this right when the algorithm converges basically and gives
算法基本上收敛，并给您转换后的结果
algorithm converges basically and gives you having converted it turns out what
you having converted it turns out what it finishes the cost will be two times
它完成的成本将是边缘数量的两倍，因为基本上
it finishes the cost will be two times the number of edges because basically in
the number of edges because basically in every answer you have to send the
您必须发送的每个答案都将消息发送回去，因为
every answer you have to send the messages going and coming back okay as
messages going and coming back okay as you see here alright so so the number of
您在这里看到的很好，所以基本上将酒精放置的步骤数
you see here alright so so the number of steps basically the alcohol is placed
steps basically the alcohol is placed two times the number of edges in in in
内边的数量是你的两倍
two times the number of edges in in in you
我是说我真的在这里尝尝
I mean I think I'm really here taste this
this so the algorithm never blocks you know
因此，该算法永远不会阻止您知道的交易，而不会发生，但是如果
so the algorithm never blocks you know for a trade without not happened but if
for a trade without not happened but if later on we will show the algorithm only
稍后我们将展示该算法仅具有循环，很有可能
later on we will show the algorithm only have loops it's very possible you have
have loops it's very possible you have an algorithm that keeps going and
保持运转并确保Everette正确的算法
an algorithm that keeps going and Everette right
Everette right keep sending message system you have
不断发送消息系统，您一直处于循环状态，并且您正在
keep sending message system you have constantly on the loop and you're in
constantly on the loop and you're in trouble all right so let me I'm gonna
麻烦您了，让我结束这个例子，因为在这个例子中
trouble all right so let me I'm gonna finish this example because is in this
finish this example because is in this is the notation that I'm using is
我使用的符号基本上就是您所知道的市场
is the notation that I'm using is basically that of you know a market on
basically that of you know a market on the field that we used before
之前我们使用过的领域，所以您知道我们有十大潜力
the field that we used before okay so you know we have ten potentials
okay so you know we have ten potentials here and if you want evidence you plug
在这里，如果您需要证据，可以将它们作为患者的两个功能插入
here and if you want evidence you plug in them two functions as patient
in them two functions as patient slightly different but this for the same
稍有不同，但这是相同的想法，所以说11个是节点
slightly different but this for the same idea so let's say eleven is the node
idea so let's say eleven is the node eleven is the root and we want to
十一是根，我们要先计算一些消息下的
eleven is the root and we want to compute the under some messages first
compute the under some messages first right and and then compute marginal and
对，然后计算边际和
实际上让我看看我们是否只想计算发生了什么
compute the under some messages first right and and then compute marginal and
actually let me see if we only want to compute what's going on okay well
实际上让我看看我们是否只想计算发生了什么
compute what's going on okay well there is no particular node of interest
没有感兴趣的特定节点，但我会告诉您这个特定的节点
there is no particular node of interest but I will tell you what this specific
but I will tell you what this specific to this example right so let's say we
对于这个示例，我们假设要计算这是根节点
to this example right so let's say we want to compute this is the root node
want to compute this is the root node right that we want to compute all the
是的，我们要计算该图上的所有消息的第10个，所以我们
right that we want to compute all the message 10th on this graph so we're
message 10th on this graph so we're going to do a first order elimination
进行一阶消除可以听到有人为我拼写什么
going to do a first order elimination can hear somebody spell for me what may
can hear somebody spell for me what may be a first order we'll look on this
首先，我们将在此图上看到许多订单
be a first order we'll look on this graph there are many orders of
graph there are many orders of eliminating nodes but here's the optimal
消除节点，但这是最优的，是一阶，你还记得自己
eliminating nodes but here's the optimal is the first order and you remember you
is the first order and you remember you start from the left tree and then from
从左边的树开始，然后从左边到外面
start from the left tree and then from the left side to outside so potentially
the left side to outside so potentially how the first order elimination will
一阶消除的外观如何1 2 1 2 3 4
how the first order elimination will look here 1 2 1 2 3 4
一二七
one two seven
好吧，所以1毫米连续体Philip 7 8 9 5 6 10和11你还是没事的
alright so 1 mm continuum Philip 7 8 9 5 6 10 and 11 you still at ok
如果您知道对您不利，但我建议您可以每周查看一次
if you know it offenders to you but I suggest is you can look at the weekly
suggest is you can look at the weekly and Wikipedia you know there is five
和Wikipedia，您知道有五种不同的订购类型，但
and Wikipedia you know there is five different types of ordering but the
different types of ordering but the first one there is basically what is
第一个基本上是用于消除三个底部的东西
first one there is basically what is used for bottom elimination on three so
used for bottom elimination on three so this is what we need to use here
这就是我们在这里需要使用的，我的意思是你还有别的
this is what we need to use here I mean you something else it's just
I mean you something else it's just assumed that part will be higher than
假设该部分将比使用孔后高，所以如果您
assumed that part will be higher than using a posthole okay so if you were
using a posthole okay so if you were gonna do calculations basically
基本上可以进行计算分析，好吧
gonna do calculations basically analytically okay so alright the
analytically okay so alright the elimination and we're gonna start to
消除，我们将开始计算消息，好吗
elimination and we're gonna start to calculate messages okay
calculate messages okay so I can calculate the message from node
所以我可以计算从节点1到7的消息，这种计算对
so I can calculate the message from node 1 to 7 is this calculation make sense to
1 to 7 is this calculation make sense to you
您没有到节点1的传入消息
you there is no incoming message to node 1
there is no incoming message to node 1 so this situation of the potential try 1
所以这种情况的潜在尝试1 7好的
so this situation of the potential try 1 7 okay
7 okay I can do a calculation of 2 to 7 at the
我可以同时进行2到7的计算，这是我可以做的
I can do a calculation of 2 to 7 at the same time no problem this is I can do
same time no problem this is I can do the calculation of 3 2 8 4 2 8 5 to 10 6
3 2 8 4 2 8 5到10 6到10的计算没关系，所以我可以
the calculation of 3 2 8 4 2 8 5 to 10 6 to 10 all right so I can do the
to 10 all right so I can do the calculation the first 2 lines all
同时在此图上计算前两行，所以现在我
calculation the first 2 lines all simultaneously on this graph so now I
simultaneously on this graph so now I need to calculate the potential from I
需要从我的意思是从7到9的消息中计算出电位，然后再次
need to calculate the potential from I mean the message from 7 to 9 and again
mean the message from 7 to 9 and again no equations are needed right so what
不需要方程式，所以您需要做的就是找到所有消息
no equations are needed right so what you need to do is find all the messages
you need to do is find all the messages are coming to notes level multiplied
即将达到的音符水平乘以7到9之间的电位，
are coming to notes level multiplied with the potential between 7 and 9 and
with the potential between 7 and 9 and get rid of 7 eliminate them
摆脱7消除它们，所以基本上从7到9的消息是
get rid of 7 eliminate them so basically the message from 7 to 9 is
so basically the message from 7 to 9 is this potential 7 9 if you can of course
这个潜在的7 9如果可以的话当然可以证明7可以，但是在
this potential 7 9 if you can of course the evidence for 7 you can but in also
the evidence for 7 you can but in also the message from 1 to 7 the message from
从1到7的消息，从2到7的消息，所以很明显，这要求
the message from 1 to 7 the message from 2 to 7 so obviously this requires that
2 to 7 so obviously this requires that you already have done this calculation
您已经以同样的方式完成了前20万的计算
you already have done this calculation the first 2 lakhs similarly you can
the first 2 lakhs similarly you can calculate the message from 8 9 ok the
从8 9确定两个消息的输入时间乘以
calculate the message from 8 9 ok the two incoming messages times this
two incoming messages times this potential and then
潜力，然后进行布局，然后让我们看看，然后
potential and then lay it out and then let's see and then
lay it out and then let's see and then we need to calculate the message from
我们需要计算从九点到十一点的信息
we need to calculate the message from nine to eleven
nine to eleven so this again nothing special the
所以这又没有什么特别的九和十一课程的潜力
so this again nothing special the potential of nine and eleven course that
potential of nine and eleven course that okay
好吧，即将来临的先生。七十九岁
okay the incoming mr. seventy-nine becoming
the incoming mr. seventy-nine becoming less to eight to nine and then
少到八到九，然后将x9集成出来，类似地
less to eight to nine and then integrating x9 out and similarly the
integrating x9 out and similarly the message compared to 11 so this time the
邮件与11相比，所以这次邮件来自今天的列表
message compared to 11 so this time the message is coming from the list today
message is coming from the list today okay now let me try the worst sort of
好吧，现在让我尝试最糟糕的基本方法来完成此操作
okay now let me try the worst sort of elementary way of completing this
elementary way of completing this message from nine to eleven right so
从9点到11点的信息，所以基本上我要在一个
message from nine to eleven right so basically I'm going to solve this in a
basically I'm going to solve this in a different mathematical form so you can
不同的数学形式，以便您可以大致了解这实际上是做什么的
different mathematical form so you can get a sense of what this actually does
get a sense of what this actually does right
对，所以消息从九点到十一点
right so the message from nine to eleven
so the message from nine to eleven effectively we start with this note we
有效地，我们从此笔记开始，我们出售信息，然后我们消除
effectively we start with this note we sell information and then we eliminate
sell information and then we eliminate the two misinformation they're in there
他们在那里的两个错误信息，然后我们消除了两个节点，然后
the two misinformation they're in there and then we eliminate two nodes and then
and then we eliminate two nodes and then from here to they are very willing in
从这里到他们在八点九分都很愿意，您知道我们
from here to they are very willing in eight nine respectively you know what we
eight nine respectively you know what we have eliminated to send a message from
消除了从9点到11点之间最多发送一条消息的时间，你能告诉我吗
have eliminated to send a message from nine to 11 with the most can you tell me
nine to 11 with the most can you tell me to eventually be ready to sent a message
最终准备好从9到11发送消息，您已经消除了
to eventually be ready to sent a message from 9 to 11 you have eliminated what
from 9 to 11 you have eliminated what you have enumerate the lots of nodes but
您已经列举了很多节点，但是这可以共同为
you have enumerate the lots of nodes but this works together some work for the
this works together some work for the subtree the comes from the left of the
子树来自左边的左边
subtree the comes from the left of the left
你看，我的意思是所有这一切，不是说这三个，如果你拿
you see that I mean all of this no it says the three that really if you take
says the three that really if you take node 11 and you can't get from there all
节点11，没有这个，您将无法从那里到达左侧的所有节点
node 11 and you can't get from there all the nodes to the left without this with
the nodes to the left without this with you demon eight so I can write this
你恶魔八，所以我可以把这个信息的汇编从九写成
you demon eight so I can write this compilation of the message from nine to
compilation of the message from nine to eleven estimation on all of these
对该子树的所有这些变量进行11个估计，我引用
eleven estimation on all of these variables of this subtree and I quote
variables of this subtree and I quote based on three the subtree that is
基于三个我移除广告911派生的子树
based on three the subtree that is derived once I remove ads 911 okay
derived once I remove ads 911 okay so this is the tree that you get once
因此，这是一棵树，一旦您将边缘从9消除为
so this is the tree that you get once you eliminate this edge from nine to
you eliminate this edge from nine to eleven
十一行，那么有效，这就是信息
eleven okay so effectively this is the message
okay so effectively this is the message this is what we have done now what also
这就是我们现在所做的，这也意味着正确，但是这种计算
this is what we have done now what also this means right but this calculation
this means right but this calculation that we had from the lessons is you can
我们从课程中学到的是，您可以从这个方程式开始，然后
that we had from the lessons is you can start from this equation all right and
start from this equation all right and we arrange the order of estimations and
我们安排估算的顺序，然后您可以重新定义这些
we arrange the order of estimations and then you can redefine again these
then you can redefine again these messages that are propagating from 1 and
从1和2传播到7的消息，从7传播到9等
messages that are propagating from 1 and 2 to 7 from seven to nine etcetera as
2 to 7 from seven to nine etcetera as part of this semester's there is nothing
这学期的一部分，没有什么特别的，这是我们做的一种方式
part of this semester's there is nothing really special it's a way that we do the
really special it's a way that we do the summations so rather than doing the
求和，而不是求和是一个大方程式
summations so rather than doing the summations is one big equation you do it
summations is one big equation you do it in some elimination order right the way
以某种消除顺序正确，就像这里讨论的那样，所以我们不要去
in some elimination order right the way that is discussed here so we don't go
that is discussed here so we don't go and do all of the summations in one
并用一个方程式完成所有求和，所以不要写计算机
and do all of the summations in one equation so don't write a computer
equation so don't write a computer program and say go and some on all of
编程说走吧，所有这一切，因为它是一棵琐碎的玩具树
program and say go and some on all of this because it's a tree of trivial toy
this because it's a tree of trivial toy problem and that's the answer you need
问题，这就是您需要计算的答案，您说浪费所有这些节点
problem and that's the answer you need to compute you say waste all these nodes
to compute you say waste all these nodes in some order and start computing is
以某种顺序开始计算是消息此，现在是其中之一
in some order and start computing is message this and one of these now this
message this and one of these now this master arrived compute you know the
主到达计算您知道从该节点传到的消息
master arrived compute you know the messages outgoing from that node to
messages outgoing from that node to another node you know and when you get
您知道的另一个节点，当您从列表中获得所有这些东西时，
another node you know and when you get all of these things from the list to the
all of these things from the list to the root then you are ready to go backwards
根，然后您就可以向后退了，这里的问题来自
root then you are ready to go backwards and here is buckled the questions from
and here is buckled the questions from awkward
尴尬的顽固与相同的消息
awkward recalcitrant of messages identical to
recalcitrant of messages identical to what we have seen before
好的之前我们已经看到了，所以让我给他
what we have seen before okay so let me give him
这些方程式中的一些，我用蓝色表示，因为我认为第一个
some of these equations and I put this things in blue because I think the first
things in blue because I think the first time I typed them not paying attention I
当我键入他们没有注意的时候，我错过了丢失这些术语的权利
time I typed them not paying attention I had missed the loss of these terms right
had missed the loss of these terms right because some of these terms you realized
因为其中一些术语使您意识到我们的信息是正确的配对
because some of these terms you realized our message the pairing from the right
our message the pairing from the right way that runs out of 11 not from the
从11开始用尽的方法不是从左侧开始的，所以让我们从节点11进行发送
way that runs out of 11 not from the left so let's take from node 11 to send
left so let's take from node 11 to send a message to node 9 what do I need to
向节点9发送消息时，我需要知道节点何时可以将消息发送至
a message to node 9 what do I need to know when a node can send messages to
know when a node can send messages to any other node
任何其他节点，我们讨论的协议是什么
any other node what is the protocol that we discussed
what is the protocol that we discussed to send the message
发送消息
好的-从11到9派了一个大师，什么时候什么协议可以
what is the protocol that we discussed to send the message
okay - sent a masters from 11 to 9 what does not what is the protocol when can
好的-从11到9派了一个大师，什么时候什么协议可以
does not what is the protocol when can 11 send the message to genomic when it
11仅从其接收到所有消息时，将消息发送到基因组
11 send the message to genomic when it only has received all messages from its
only has received all messages from its neighbors and the neighbors here except
邻居和这里的邻居，除了9之外没有10很好，所以11会发送一个
neighbors and the neighbors here except 9 is no 10 alright so for 11 to send a
9 is no 10 alright so for 11 to send a message to 911 history see the rest is
信息到911历史，看到其余的是10起，他需要没有发布信息
message to 911 history see the rest is from 10 he needs to have no post message
from 10 he needs to have no post message on here all right obviously captain
在这里好吧，显然是图片中的船长，但是错过了
on here all right obviously captain based in the picture but missed the
based in the picture but missed the message that pen sends to you ever all
笔向您发送的消息没事，所以基本上来自11的消息
message that pen sends to you ever all right so basically the message from 11
right so basically the message from 11 to 9 is this potential with the message
到9是这种潜力，消息从10到11，然后是节点11
to 9 is this potential with the message coming from 10 to 11 and then node 11
coming from 10 to 11 and then node 11 eliminate similarly if you want to
如果要计算承租人11美分到10的费用，则消除类似
eliminate similarly if you want to compute the lessees 11 cents to 10 would
compute the lessees 11 cents to 10 would be the potential of 11 and 10 and the
是11和10的潜力，以及来自9-11等信息，等等
be the potential of 11 and 10 and the message coming from 9-11 etc etc okay
所以呈现的奥秘，基本上，如果你想说一个物理的
so the mystery of presenting and so basically if you want to say a physical
basically if you want to say a physical sort of interpretation of the
我们对发送消息所做的计算的某种解释
sort of interpretation of the calculation we did for sending a message
calculation we did for sending a message 11 from 11 to 9 effectively what you can
从11到9的11实际上，如果您看对了，您可以想象的是
11 from 11 to 9 effectively what you can envision is if you look at the right
envision is if you look at the right subtree right the subtree basically that
子树基本上是当您消除X 9到11时得到的子树
subtree right the subtree basically that you get when you eliminate the X 9 to 11
you get when you eliminate the X 9 to 11 all right and then you do elimination of
好，然后您消除子树中的所有节点，然后
all right and then you do elimination of all the nodes in the subtree okay and
all the nodes in the subtree okay and that means you some on 5 to 10 and 11 of
这意味着您可能会在5至10和11的电势中
that means you some on 5 to 10 and 11 of the potentials corresponding to this
the potentials corresponding to this subject okay so if you do this basically
主题很好，所以如果您基本上这样做，您将获得的是
subject okay so if you do this basically what you will get is you will get this
what you will get is you will get this calculation at the end of the day okay
在一天结束时进行计算还可以，但是显然，这为您提供了一种方法
calculation at the end of the day okay but obviously this gives you a way to
but obviously this gives you a way to remember so I don't have time to finish
记住，所以我没有时间完成这145，但是我建议看一下
remember so I don't have time to finish this 145 but what I suggest this look at
this 145 but what I suggest this look at the algorithm because there is a stream
该算法，因为有一个流和局部同上的复杂
the algorithm because there is a stream and the local ibid sort of complicated
and the local ibid sort of complicated so the algorithm for setting the
因此，用于设置后继订单的算法总是非常先进的
so the algorithm for setting the postorder it's very progressive always
postorder it's very progressive always 25 lines okay and it does this correctly
25行就可以了，它正确执行了，算法的总和将
25 lines okay and it does this correctly okay and the sum for the algorithms will
okay and the sum for the algorithms will describe this basically little
描述这个与消除算法基本上没有什么区别
describe this basically little difference from elimination algorithm
difference from elimination algorithm and it is the custom in there in nature
这是自然界中的习惯，例如在收集消息之前
and it is the custom in there in nature for example collecting messages before
for example collecting messages before you are ready to propagate it's a
您准备好传播它是一个递归算法，甚至是树
you are ready to propagate it's a recursive algorithm even tree
recursive algorithm even tree distributing message from a node to the
从节点到腿部举动的消息传递也是一种递归算法
distributing message from a node to the leg lifts is also a recursive algorithm
leg lifts is also a recursive algorithm so I'm really like you know you guys to
所以我真的很想你知道你们尝试至少编程
so I'm really like you know you guys to make an attempt to at least program
make an attempt to at least program something that involves inference on
涉及扭曲推断的东西，因为你们都在前进
something that involves inference on twist because sort of an is y'all going
twist because sort of an is y'all going okay so and as I mentioned those who are
好的，正如我提到的，如果您不是真的在审核课程，
okay so and as I mentioned those who are auditing the course if you don't really
auditing the course if you don't really program these things there is no way
对这些东西进行编程实际上是没有办法的
program these things there is no way actually
actually you'll never figure out how this thing
你永远不会弄清楚这东西现在是如何工作的，如果
you'll never figure out how this thing works now if